<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news.atom"/>
  <title>iWholesaleCandy.ca - Sweet Candy News</title>
  <updated>2021-03-18T16:43:17-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>iWholesaleCandy.ca</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/canadas-largest-demographic-is-buying-candy</id>
    <published>2021-03-18T16:43:17-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-03-18T16:43:18-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/canadas-largest-demographic-is-buying-candy"/>
    <title>The Largest Demographic is Buying Candy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Boomers "used to be" the biggest demo group – are you now focusing on the NEWEST and fastest growing group of potential customers?<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/canadas-largest-demographic-is-buying-candy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>As recently as five years ago, we were all made aware of the booming "Boomers" market – but did you know there is another booming group of consumers that is surpassing this demographic? At iWholesale Candy, we share the need to know exactly who your biggest consumer is, and it's no longer the 'Boomer'... </p>
<p>Boomers in Canada are recognized as those individuals born between 1946 and 1964. Right now, it means they're typically in their mid-to-late 60s and early 70s. And yes, they are buying candy – but the face of candy purchases is quickly changing.  </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_2.39.55_PM_240x240.png?v=1616097825" alt="" width="522" height="259"></p>
<p>Between Generation X, Y and now Z, fast approaching Generation Y (or Millennials) are those born between 1981 and 1995, are foreseen to take over as the largest demographic in Canada within the next few years, and iWholesaleCandy thinks you should be focusing on them now – sooner rather than later. This group is just over 10 million people in Canada.</p>
<h3>Notable points iWholesaleCandy recommends you know about Millennials in Canada:</h3>
<ul>
<li>They have been incorrectly labeled as the laziest, most temperamental age group, yet they are incredibly loyal to the brands like like. If your store is able to get them in, they're more likely to remain as loyal customers. Offer them something they can rely on and they like, and they'll keep coming back.</li>
<li>39% of them have a Bachelor's Degree or higher, compared with just 15% of Baby Boomers. This means that, combined with their aptitude for electronics, they are researching the best place, pricing, ingredients, and quality of goods than ever before. A website - even a simple one - is recommended in order to reach and retain them.</li>
<li>Buying power: They are more likely to come in as groups and buy more from you than any other generation. They spend a lot of time on electronics (on average 7 hours per day in Canada) but when they go out, they do it typically in 'herds' or larger groups. If one comes in, many come in. And you must allow for their favourites to be on display (see next point, below).</li>
<li>Millennials are looking for the unusual, the different, the super-flavourful, and the long-lasting. According to studies, they are really enjoying those sweets and treats that pack a punch. They're looking for more choice when it comes to flavours, textures, pack sizes and price. They are essentially looking for <em>variety</em>.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Candy and treats suggested for Millennials:</h3>
<p>Here are some iWholesale Candy suggestions you should consider next time you're placing an order online for the best wholesale candy that will attract Canada's largest demographic of candy purchasers:</p>
<p><strong>Gummies</strong></p>
<p>Look for different, unusual, not-so-familiar brands that are delicious and colourful items that your customer cannot find anywhere else.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.06.52_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098556" alt="" width="198" height="127"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.10.30_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098579" alt="" width="172" height="170"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.17.06_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098650" alt="" width="156" height="185"></p>
<p><strong>Sour</strong></p>
<p>Taking your customer to a world of exploring sour candies with much more than they have ever considered, and past the most-known treats they may have grown up with. iWholesaleCandy believes that millennials are trend-setters, and if they catch on to a new or more unusually-seen product they can bring in a whole new group of clients to your store.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.18.22_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098736" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.18.15_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098752" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-03-18_at_4.18.04_PM_240x240.png?v=1616098773" alt=""></p>
<p><strong>Chocolate - always a winner</strong></p>
<p>Chocolate is a big seller for this rapidly growing demographic. As we've discussed, since Millennials are trend-setters and they like their unusual sweets that they can share with fellow Millennial friends, this makes for a winning combination and a great, long-lasting customer. The key here at iWholesaleCandy is: VARIETY and offering products they have yet to find anywhere else, in any of their usual stores. </p>
<p><strong>Bulk Options</strong></p>
<p>As we know in the candy bulk business, having bulk options is a big seller - regardless of the demographic or what your buyer is looking to buy. The option for them to choose from a few grams (or a whole kilo!) of different types of candies is very important. This is one of the reasons why iWholesaleCandy is the best option for buying candy in bulk online: Selection!</p>
<p>Our best advice at iWholesaleCandy is to take a closer look at the customer that is coming in to your store: What is their age group? What are they looking for? Which areas of your store are they walking through – what are their eyeballs looking at, and are they finding what they seek? Soon you will come to see patterns and this can make a big difference not only in the candies and treats they buy, but also in how much of a long-term relationship they form with you, their favourite store. </p>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">#iWholesaleCandy #buyCandyonline #bulkcandy #bulkcandyonline #bulkcandyCanada #covid19candy #celebrateSpring #wholesaleCandySales #bulkCanada #candyCanada #marketinginspiration #marketingideas #candyideas #buyinbulk #bestonlinecandy #bestbulkcandy #CanadaCandy</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/theatre-boxes-they-want-it-bigger</id>
    <published>2021-02-25T18:24:29-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-25T18:24:58-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/theatre-boxes-they-want-it-bigger"/>
    <title>Theatre Boxes: They Want it Bigger!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Remember what going to the movies was like? The smell of popcorn, the buzz, the massive boxes of candy? Bring it all back with movie night Theatre Boxes of Candy and treats.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/theatre-boxes-they-want-it-bigger">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Remember what going to the movies was like? The atmosphere, the scent of freshly popped buttery popcorn, the slushies and massive boxes of candy? Bring the larger theatre boxes of candy to your customer and help them have an excellent indulgence of movies and candy this weekend!</p>
<p>Although some customers may want a few of the different candies in the smaller sized packages, no doubt there are many of us at iWholesale Candy that are looking for <strong>BIGGER OPTIONS</strong> - and customers are no different. </p>
<p>Remember this: 2021 may mean tighter budgets – but <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/2021-tighter-budgets-but-not-for-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>NOT FOR CANDY! </strong></a></p>
<p>The psychology of buying bigger, for many people, is a chance to truly indulge and give yourself a pat on the back for having completed a full week of work or study. Now it's time to reward yourself!</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.06.09_PM_480x480.png?v=1614294395" alt="" width="518" height="349"></p>
<p>iWholesale Candy has a large selection of Theatre Boxes for sale that you can order online. These candies are not for the weak sweet tooth – they are especially designed for those who want to truly enjoy and feel fulfilled. </p>
<p>There is a market for these Theatre Boxes of candy, and iWholesale Candy has them for you to choose from.  </p>
<h3>Theatre Box Gummies</h3>
<p>These adorably and deliciously fruit-flavoured bites are made for those who are a kid at heart – and for the stressed out candy-fan! The sole act of chewing is a stress reliever!</p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.11.21_PM_480x480.png?v=1614294718" alt="" width="244" height="219"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.11.33_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294731" alt=""></p>
<h3>Theatre Box Licorice Treats</h3>
<p>Licorice is adored by more customers than you would imagine! They are a special treat for those who aren't necessarily looking for something too sweet, but still want a treat – and they love their licorice! </p>
<div style="text-align: left;">
<img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.57.32_PM_480x480.png?v=1614294432" style="float: none;" width="253" height="253"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.57.42_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294572" alt="">
</div>
<h3>Theatre Box Crunchy Snacks</h3>
<p>You can't just have one, and the small packs are just too small! These Theatre Box sized crunchy snacks are good enough for sharing since there are lots in a package. iWholesale Candy thinks they're perfect for Movie Night with the family – and these days we're all doing a lot more of that!</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.00.21_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294474" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.00.39_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294495" alt=""></p>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.01.09_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294519" alt="" style="float: none;"></div>
<h3>Theatre Box Classics</h3>
<p>Because you can't get enough of these candies that are so good, there just isn't enough in a small pack! Perfect for sharing, or even for keeping in the car since they can stay fresh for so long! (Plus, they make a long drive more easeful too).</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.58.42_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294762" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.11.08_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294743" alt=""></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.14.23_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294882" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_6.14.11_PM_240x240.png?v=1614294898" alt=""></p>
<p>Carry a whole selection of these larger Theatre Box candies and treats and place them together in a section at your store. You will begin to notice your customer is willing to spend that bit extra on their treats before the weekend, before game-time, and especially for movie night to alongside their popcorn and specialty drinks. Because sometimes, they just want it bigger.  </p>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">#iWholesaleCandy #buyCandyonline #bulkcandy #bulkcandyonline #bulkcandyCanada #covid19candy #celebrateSpring #wholesaleCandySales #bulkCanada #candyCanada </span><span class="s2">#marketinginspiration #marketingideas #candyideas #threatreboxcandy #largercandy #wantmorecandy #morecandy #candyideas #movienightideas #movienightcandy</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/springtime-candy-you-must-carry</id>
    <published>2021-02-25T17:41:09-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-25T17:43:49-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/springtime-candy-you-must-carry"/>
    <title>The Key to Springtime Candy Sales Success</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Springtime is here and there are many celebrations around the corner for your customer. Here are some ideas for your marketing success this spring:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/springtime-candy-you-must-carry">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>After what seems like a long winter, Spring is finally around the corner and with it, so many things are happening! How can you carry all of the important seasonal treats your customers are looking for, without breaking the budget? </p>
<p>iWholesale Candy is your best source for these answers, and here's where to start:</p>
<h2>Candy by colour</h2>
<p>This is one of the things about springtime that most excites customers: The brightness of the colours that are popping up everywhere! Bright springtime colours are typically pastel colours – such as pink, light blue and green, baby yellow, and white. The alternative is a primary colour scheme such as blue, red and green, bright yellow, and red. iWholesale Candy recommends that these primary colours remind the customer that it's a time of excitement, that spring is here!</p>
<h3>Here are some ideas for candy with both colour schemes:</h3>
<p>First, let's take a look at the pastels , which remind the customer that Easter is coming – a time for renewal, new babies, bunnies, Mother's Day, cake and candies! Here are some of our suggestions:</p>
<p><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/4d-gummy-unicorns-112g-24ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bazooka Gummy Unicorns</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/barbie-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Barbie Surprise Eggs</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/disney-frozen-surprise-eggs-24-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Disney Frozen 'Surprise' Eggs</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-bottle-caps-rolls" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bottle Caps Candy Rolls</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/candy-bracelets-10-pack-18ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Candy Creations Candy Bracelets</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/charms-fluffy-stuff-cotton-candy-2-5oz-24ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Charms Fluffy Stuff Cotton Candy</a></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.53.14_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291547" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.54.27_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291565" alt="" width="105" height="158"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.55.08_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291589" alt="" width="180" height="201"></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.56.01_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291616" alt="" width="206" height="167"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.56.50_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291636" alt="" width="132" height="172"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_4.57.48_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291659" alt="" width="196" height="181"></p>
<p>Now let's take a look at the primary coloured bulk candy ideas you can buy online through iWholesale Candy, and you can visually see the difference in your store – and your customer will as well!</p>
<p><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/4d-gummy-fruits-112g-24ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">4D Gummy Fruits</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/air-heads-xtremes-belts-rainbow-berry-57g" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Air Heads Xtreme Belt Rainbows</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/albanese-gummi-awesome-blossoms" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Albanese Gummi Awesome Blossoms</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/alberts-swirl-pops" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Albert's Swirl Pops</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/bakugan-laser-pop-12ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bakugan Laser Pop</a>.</p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.00.02_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291699" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.00.58_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291722" alt=""></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.01.57_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291743" alt="" width="181" height="172"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.02.42_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291768" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.03.48_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291787" alt=""></p>
<p>The customer has become a lot more savvy about their candy purchases, especially at a time like spring, when there is so much happening and there are so many opportunities for candy-giving! They are looking for things to cheer them up and ideas of little presents to cheer their family on as well. </p>
<h2>They want the New Stuff too</h2>
<p>Your customer is looking for a treat, so why not offer them what they're looking for but also what's new in store? There is no better way than to grow customer loyalty than to offer them something new to look forward to, such as these delicious treats to try:</p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.17.44_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291813" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.18.18_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291831" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.18.24_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291850" alt=""></p>
<meta charset="utf-8">
<p><strong>Check out iWholesale Candy's New Candy collection <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">[HERE]</a>.</strong></p>
<h2>Don't forget the Retro Candy!</h2>
<p>There is a reason why iWholesale Candy has become the #1 online bulk candy store in Canada: We carry a wide assortment of candies, chocolates and treats! Not just novelty candy, but the retro candy sold online as well. </p>
<p>These Retro Candy ideas are ones which never go out of style, and your customer has come to love them – regardless of age. You must give them the choice of both Retro candy and New candy, in order to keep them coming back to you as 'THE BEST CANDY SUPPLIER' for everything they're looking for! Such as: </p>
<p><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/retro-candy/products/mccraws-giant-taffy-24-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">McCraw's Giant Taffy</a> • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=pop*%20rocks*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Pop Rocks Candy and Bubble Gum</a> (available in a variety of flavours!) • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/retro-candy/products/hersheys-kisses-330-pieces" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hershey's Kisses</a> (they're looking for freshness, so be sure to keep them fresh!) • <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/retro-candy/products/nik-l-nip-wax-bottles-candy-4-packs" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nik-L-Nip Wax Bottles Candy</a>.</p>
<p> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.08.05_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291971" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.09.05_PM_240x240.png?v=1614291987" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.10.09_PM_240x240.png?v=1614292006" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-25_at_5.13.31_PM_240x240.png?v=1614292037" alt=""></p>
<p>There is a certain psychology behind making a retail store successful, and candy can certainly draw in your customers this spring - and the whole year through. With iWholesale Candy's advice, you'll keep them coming back for more to see what else is new, and old... as well as for inspiration, which they'll appreciate from their favourite store. </p>
<h2>Happy Springtime! It's candy time!</h2>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">#iWholesaleCandy #buyCandyonline #bulkcandy #bulkcandyonline #bulkcandyCanada #Eastercandy #Easterfavourites #celebrateEaster #Eastertreats #covid19candy #celebrateSpring #wholesaleCandySales #bulkCanada #candyCanada #marketinginspiration #marketingideas #candyideas </span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-the-perfect-easter-gift-bag</id>
    <published>2021-02-16T18:26:42-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-16T18:26:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-the-perfect-easter-gift-bag"/>
    <title>Making the Perfect Easter Gift Bag</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[It's important to be creative when selling candy at your store. The Easter Gift Bag is a great idea you can easily customize for any visitor to your store to get inspired! Here's how to do it:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-the-perfect-easter-gift-bag">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Just like your customers think, at iWholesale Candy we believe having one single candy is just never enough. It takes a variety to satisfy a sweet tooth, and Easter is the one of the best times of year to do just that.</p>
<p>It's important to be creative when selling candy at your store, and to show your customer ideas on how they can do this too. Putting together a few Easter Gift Bags will not only give your customer the idea of what they can also do, but they may even buy the whole gift bag that you've prepared! It's a great marketing idea for selling your candy. Here's how to do it: </p>
<h3>Variety: The sweet spice of life!</h3>
<p>We're all created with different tastes, that's what makes the perfect customer. For some, it's all about chocolate, for others, it's mint or maybe licorice. Easter is a celebration of all things 'new' – a time for your customer to experience some of this variety. </p>
<p>It may be the same candies they've become fond of over the years, or it may be a time to mix it up and try something new. This is where the Easter Gift Bag comes in!</p>
<h3>1. Tug at their heart strings: Start with their favourites</h3>
<p>iWholesale Candy has the largest variety of favourite candy in bulk for you to choose from, to make a selection for your customers. Some of the favourites may not necessarily be Easter-related, but it will catch their attention! Some of the favourite candies may include <strong>Maltesers Chocolate Candy,</strong> <strong>Hershey's Milk Chocolate Candy Bars,</strong> and <strong>M&amp;M's</strong> – their go-to favourites.  </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.46.43_PM_240x240.png?v=1613515870" alt="" width="221" height="199"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.47.08_PM_240x240.png?v=1613515888" alt="" width="245" height="134"></p>
<h3>2. Add their favourites – with a twist! </h3>
<p>As such, your customer will then move on to catching the newer versions of their favourites, like these White Chocolate M&amp;M's or the M&amp;M Pretzel Chocolate Candies, or the deliciously tantalizing M&amp;M Crispy Chocolate Candies. </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.49.38_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516322" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.49.42_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516340" alt=""></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.50.03_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516360" alt=""></p>
<h3>3. Pops of colour</h3>
<p>iWholesale Candy online bulk candy store believes the Perfect Easter Gift Bag should <em>always</em> contain some of the most colourful candy that your customer may not have had in a while. These sweet treats may be Blow Pop Lollipops, Bazooka Candy Ring Pops, or a fun-time Swirl Pop – <em>don't YOU remember having some too? </em></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.56.13_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516986" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.56.40_PM_240x240.png?v=1613517003" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.57.17_PM_240x240.png?v=1613517021" alt=""></p>
<h3>4. The little bits of sweet candies</h3>
<p>Don't forget to carry the small lose candies your customer can throw in a gift bag that will fill the spaces in between the larger pieces. These items can make the gift bag or goodie bag look full and enticing, like with the traditional Dubble Bubble gum, the Koala Fried Egg Candies – and also have them rip open a bag of Waterbridge Mini Allsorts in there! </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_6.03.59_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516879" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_6.05.36_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516899" alt="" width="151" height="152"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_6.02.33_PM_240x240.png?v=1613516920" alt=""></p>
<p>It's important to carry a variety and also to put together some sample bags for your customer to see what this may look like. Not everyone is creative at gift-giving, and Easter is a time when we all love to share in the sweet and exciting time that Easter is all about, so ideas are what will drive your customer to keep coming back to your store for unique ideas!</p>
<h3>What kind of items would you like to see in your Easter Gift Bag? Share with your comments below! </h3>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p class="p1"><span class="s1">#iWholesaleCandy #buyCandyonline #bulkcandy #bulkcandyonline #bulkcandyCanada #Eastercandy #Easterfavourites #celebrateEaster #Eastertreats #covid19candy #celebrateSpring #wholesaleCandySales #bulkCanada #candyCanada #giftideas #bulkgifts #candymarketingideas </span></p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-up-with-easter-candy-sales</id>
    <published>2021-02-16T17:33:59-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-02-16T17:35:42-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-up-with-easter-candy-sales"/>
    <title>So many Easter eggs to choose from!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[It's never too soon to order your bulk candy online through iWholesaleCandy.ca - especially when it comes to the exciting time of Easter! Here's what your customer is expecting:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-up-with-easter-candy-sales">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Easter will be here before you know it, and if you haven't stocked up your store for Easter sales, now's the time to do it!</p>
<p>It's never too soon to start an Easter Candy display. It gets people in the mood for spring-season, plus it plants the seed in your customer's mind that YOUR STORE is the one to go to when they're ready!</p>
<p>Easter is a time for celebration for many people, and for many reasons; it's a significant time of year to sell candy at your store, and one of the busiest times at iWholesale Candy online candy sales! It signifies a religious time, it also tells your customer spring is here and with it, the beginning of warmer climate, gardening, and spending more time outdoors.</p>
<h2>They get the colour scheme</h2>
<p>Customers gravitate toward colours for many reasons: At Christmas-time it's red and green, Valentine's Day it's red (and chocolate!) while at Easter it's the sweet variety of pastels. Those baby blues and yellows, the loving pink colour, even white and light green. It's a happy time and a great time for your customer to fill up on candy!</p>
<h2>Good memories with Easter candy</h2>
<p>Chances are, your customer has celebrated Easter as a child – whatever their beliefs are. At iWholesale Candy, we offer a great amount of candy online sales before Easter, because our customers see a large increase of sales during this time: The customer is happy; the customer wants to celebrate; they want to pass on the good memories they experienced as a child, on to their kids too. </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.35.09_PM_480x480.png?v=1613514929" alt="" width="508" height="211"></p>
<h2>Easter favourites: The chocolate egg!</h2>
<p>Some of the classics at Easter time never get 'old', like chocolate eggs and especially those with a toy surprise inside like the classic Kinder Surprise. They have now also been modernized, catering to the now-youngster who loves their <strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/barbie-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct?_pos=2&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Barbie</a></strong>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/paw-patrol-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct?_pos=6&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Paw Patrol</strong></a>, and even to <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/nhl-chocolate-egg-24-ct?_pos=1&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>NHL Hockey</strong></a> fans! Take a look at these newbie candies you must carry in your store and immediately <strong>order</strong> from iWholesale Candy!</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.13.58_PM_240x240.png?v=1613513739" alt="" width="147" height="211"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.14.03_PM_240x240.png?v=1613513757" alt="" width="142" height="203"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.15.12_PM_240x240.png?v=1613513779" alt="" width="195" height="227"></p>
<p>iWholesale Candy also provides the BEST and most innovative new Easter candy for sale for your store, including the <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/unicorn-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct?_pos=3&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Unicorn Surprise Eggs</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/marvel-spiderman-surprise-eggs-24-ct?_pos=5&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Marvel Spiderman Surprise Eggs</strong></a>, <strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/disney-frozen-surprise-eggs-24-ct?_pos=4&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Disney 'Frozen' Eggs</a></strong>, and of course <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/hot-wheels-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct?_pos=7&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Hot Wheels Eggs</strong></a>, <strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/shimmer-n-shine-surprise-eggs-20g-24ct?_pos=12&amp;_sid=55f81b00b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Shimmer and Shine Eggs</a></strong>, and <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=egg*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[LOTS MORE]</strong></a>. </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.22.36_PM_240x240.png?v=1613514184" alt="" width="182" height="195"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.22.40_PM_240x240.png?v=1613514198" alt="" width="174" height="203"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-02-16_at_5.22.26_PM_240x240.png?v=1613514224" alt="" width="164" height="177"></p>
<h2>Variety is the key to success (and return customers)</h2>
<p>The key to selling many eggs at your store this Easter is to offer a large variety of them – this way you can tug at your customer's heart strings and entice them to not just buy one per child, or family member, but many. There are such a large variety at iWholesale Candy that you can buy in bulk online within Canada, it'll keep your customer visiting and buying at your store on a regular basis – because you will show them you are IN when it comes to the best treats and sweets.</p>
<h3>Which kind of bulk candy are you going to have at your store this Easter, that you haven't had yet? Please comment below:</h3>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p>#iWholesaleCandy #buyCandyonline #bulkcandy #bulkcandyonline #bulkcandyCanada #Eastercandy #Easterfavourites #celebrateEaster #Eastertreats #covid19candy #celebrateSpring #wholesaleCandySales #bulkCanada #candyCanada </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-march-break-happen</id>
    <published>2021-01-29T15:11:12-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-29T15:13:28-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-march-break-happen"/>
    <title>Making March Break Happen</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Times may have changed, but people have not! We all still need the break, so here are some great ideas to grow client loyalty.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/making-march-break-happen">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Yes, times may have (temporarily) changed, but people generally have not. They are still looking to celebrate the 'special times of year' and you are there to help them do just that. </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-29_at_3.04.12_PM_480x480.png?v=1611950682" alt=""></p>
<p>March Break has long been a time for families to reunite: Kids were off school for a whole week, young adult University or College attendees fly back home to spend time with the family, and many parents worked to make their March Break vacation to coincide. </p>
<p>For many, it was a time to fly somewhere south and take a break from the cold. Now, and as our shopping experience changes, we are pondering what will this March Break look like? The iWholesale Candy team and favourite candy bulk  provider suggests "Making March Break Happen". </p>
<p>This will actually be a good opportunity for retailers, as people will be enjoying the "Stay-cation" – a chance to stay at home and celebrate with those we love, while staying safe in our own nest. It's will all be about how the retailer approaches it, and how they suggest the consumer make the best of their spending dollar. Here are some iWholesale Candy suggestions you can dress up your outlet with, and in turn empower your customer to one of the following candy ideas for March Break:</p>
<h3><strong>Saying "Welcome Home" with candy:</strong></h3>
<div style="text-align: left;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/candy_basket_240x240.jpg?v=1611950828" alt="" style="margin-right: 12px; float: left;"></div>
<p>Prepare a small gift basket display for your customers to buy so they can gift their school-aged students as a gift. Make sure you fill it with colourful treats that they will enjoy through the Stay-cation March Break event. They will be able to decorate their homes with streamers and balloons, and give each of their children a Welcome Home basket. Instant smile!</p>
<h3><strong></strong></h3>
<h3><strong>Plan a March Break "Summer Camp":</strong></h3>
<p>For parents with smaller kids, they can plan a mock "Summer Camp" where kids will be dressed in shorts and t-shirts, and drink lemonade, Tang, Kool-Aid, and all those delicious drinks they are not usually entitled to have. Suggest they can plan a special outing per day on a hike, to come home and enjoy their favourite treats.</p>
<h3>March Break "Crafty Time" Week:</h3>
<p>This is good for any age, as many children and adults enjoy crafting – either learning something new or making the time to do something they don't usually get the time to do: Sew, paint, cook, do some woodworking... And what better than to intertwine candy into the crafty-time creations? </p>
<p><strong>Remember:</strong> As the retailer, YOU are their inspiration for your customer. They come to you looking to buy a particular candy, but it will be up to you to suggest ideas for them, and entice them to try the [NEW CANDY] they can enjoy. Make this March Break idea an important one for them!</p>
<p>They will be thankful and come back as a loyal customer... Because sometimes growing loyalty takes time and energy, and as a retailer, you can reap the rewards of being their "favourite store"!</p>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/2021-tighter-budgets-but-not-for-candy</id>
    <published>2021-01-29T14:46:38-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-29T14:46:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/2021-tighter-budgets-but-not-for-candy"/>
    <title>2021: Tighter budgets, but not for candy!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1"><span class="s1">In a challenging world, candy is always there to comfort us. Learn why the trend to buy candy continues, especially as times get tough. </span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/2021-tighter-budgets-but-not-for-candy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p>This year is well on its way and for many consumers, it will be the year for them to tighten the budget in many ways. Candy, on the other hand, is something they are not willing to budge on – iWholesale Candy explores why.</p>
<p>Navigating the challenges of a Pandemic has proven quite difficult for many retailers, if not all, and it has forced us to "think outside of the box". </p>
<p>Consumer have become much more savvy when it comes to buying their supplies online – from clothes to groceries. As budgets tighten at home and office, many consumers are foregoing frivolous expenses and turning to feel-good spending. According to research firm<span> </span><a href="https://www.nielsen.com/ca/en/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nielsen</a>, 48% of consumers are looking for deals and shopping at stores that offer discounts and coupons. As such, make it easier for your customer to see your in-store specials and carry the latest candy trends as well as their favourites, to keep them coming back. </p>
<h2><strong>What are consumers spending their money on?</strong></h2>
<p>Naturally, spending habits have changed. We are focused on making our homes more comfortable, buying new furniture, computers and gadgets to ease work-at-home, and fixing things that needed looking after for years – such as the fence or walkway, however Nielsen also suggests this year we're looking for more shelf-stable products that will bring joy to our lives. </p>
<p><strong>Enter candy:</strong> The one food that can bring satisfaction as a treat. iWholesale Candy can offer this advice to our B2B business clients and to all those who are seeking financial reward from their retail business: <em>Candy satisfies!</em></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/office_food_480x480.jpg?v=1611949010" alt=""></p>
<p>Focus on reaching the consumer by pulling at their heart strings, as candy can also be considered a comfort food. Candy can bring comfort, it can relax the mind, even the chewing motion or the many benefits of eating chocolate<span> </span><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-candies-to-relieve-stress" target="_blank" title="candy for stress" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[READ OUR BLOG HERE]</strong></a><span> </span>can help your customer have a grand day. </p>
<p>So whilst the consumer is not able to travel, gather in groupings, host festivities, or openly see their family and friends, they are able to enjoy the small things in life that will satisfy them – among them, candy. </p>
<p>Suggest to your customer that it is possible to have an in-house candy party by purchasing a variety of textures, flavours, colours, and display them in a fun way, and they will be immediately interested in learning more.</p>
<p>Candy is here to stay, and iWholesale Candy is able to provide our customers with everything they need to order bulk candy online. </p>
<p><strong>What type of candy do you think would satisfy the most? Ask your customer. Comment below. And contact us for all your online bulk candy supplies. </strong></p>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p>#iwholesalecandy #candyonline #bulkcandy #bulksweets #chocolateparty #CanadianCandy #AmericanCandy #noveltyCandy #bestCandySupplier #Candy #favouriteCandy #WholesaleCandyOnline</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/new-year-arrivals-you-must-carry</id>
    <published>2021-01-11T12:30:13-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-11T12:33:52-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/new-year-arrivals-you-must-carry"/>
    <title>New year arrivals you MUST carry!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[With so much variety, how do you know which candy is best to carry? What will your customer want to buy – new or old favourites?<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/new-year-arrivals-you-must-carry">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>iWholesale Candy knows there's a lot of competition when it comes to the candy world: There's so much variety, how can you carry it all?</p>
<p><strong>The simple answer</strong> – and the most obvious one – is that, you don't. Your customer will come looking for something in particular, and if they don't find it, they will most likely try something else. Right?</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_12.32.13_PM_480x480.png?v=1610386354" alt="" width="515" height="342"></p>
<p>Other times <em>(and reports say that this happens 80% of the time</em>) they know they're looking for a treat but don't have a clear idea of exactly what, so they come in to your establishment for inspiration. </p>
<p><strong>Here's where new candy arrivals come in! </strong></p>
<p>iWholesale Candy advises that it's important to carry the ones that your customer considers their "favourite" as well as the new ones they haven't even seen before – and let's face it, ordering bulk candy online has never been as user-friendly as before! </p>
<h3>Here are some of this year's new candy arrivals you probably haven't seen or heard of, but your customer will love to try:</h3>
<p><strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/milky-way-salted-caramel-bars-24-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Milky Way Salted Caramel Bars</a> –</strong> With a beautiful blend of both sweet and salty.</p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_11.55.00_AM_480x480.png?v=1610384193" alt=""></p>
<h3>Some of their favourites, reinvented!</h3>
<p>Including <strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/cow-tales-chocolate-brownie-candy-36-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cow Tales Chocolate Brownie Candy</a></strong> and <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/mrs-freshleys-reeses-peanut-butter-flavored-cupcakes-6-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Reese's Peanut Butter Flavoured Cupcakes</strong></a>... that's right, a cupcake! </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_11.57.01_AM_480x480.png?v=1610384359" alt="" width="250" height="412"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_11.57.05_AM_480x480.png?v=1610384375" alt="" width="228" height="409"></p>
<p>Some of these items don't take that much shelf space either, and are SO WORTH having in stock, as your customer will go crazy over them!</p>
<p>For example, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/toxic-waste-atomz-12-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Toxic Waste Atomz</strong></a>, which are "hazardously sour", <strong><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/moon-pie-banana-double-decker-2-75oz-12ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Moonpie Banana Double Decker,</a> </strong> Koko's Confectionery <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/cupcake-popping-candy-53oz-20ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Cupcake Popping Candy</strong></a>, and the crowd pleaser <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/starburst-blue-raspberry-singles-to-go-drink-mix-12-ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Starburst Blue Raspberry Singles-to-go Drink Mix.</strong></a> </p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_12.00.54_PM_480x480.png?v=1610384589" alt="" width="226" height="325"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_12.03.53_PM_480x480.png?v=1610384694" alt="" width="294" height="301"></p>
<p><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_12.05.32_PM_480x480.png?v=1610384829" alt="" width="270" height="329"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-11_at_12.06.41_PM_480x480.png?v=1610384850" alt="" width="179" height="302"></p>
<p>The customer that is looking for a special treat, just wants to be in 'AWE' of the candy specialties you carry, and iWholesale Candy is here to support your business by offering the best New Candy online store for your order. </p>
<p><strong>Check out iWholesale Candy's <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">NEW ARRIVALS</a> and let's make this your best year of candy sales ever! </strong></p>
<p>- - - -</p>
<p>#candyonline #wholesaleCandy #iwholesale #buycandyonline #ordercanadiancandy #bulkcandy #bulkcanadiancandy #newcandy #candy2021 #newcandyarrivals #innovativecandy #candystore #onlinecandystore #newsnacks #newchocolates #lovecandy #indulge #limitededitioncandy #2021candy #iwholesalecandy #newcandycanada</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/with-so-much-candy-why-buy-gum</id>
    <published>2021-01-04T12:18:10-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-04T12:18:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/with-so-much-candy-why-buy-gum"/>
    <title>With so much candy: Why buy gum?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span>iWholesale Candy will show you the many reasons why chewing gum is not just good for you, but how to use it as a marketing tool for building rapport and trust with your customers.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/with-so-much-candy-why-buy-gum">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">It’s a funny thing to think about, this chewing gum thing… Can you only imagine what the caveman would’ve thought about it? Chewing for sometimes hours on end, a piece of flavoured food you just don’t swallow!</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_11.52.20_AM_480x480.png?v=1609779869" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"><em><strong>Through this blog, iWholesale Candy will show you the many reasons why chewing gum is not only good for you, but how to use it as a marketing tool for building rapport and trust with your customers.</strong></em></p>
<p class="p1">The history of chewing gum has always fascinated us at iWholesale Candy. In short, it has been with us for centuries and brought to life by Thomas Adams in 1818 when he tried making synthetic rubber and ended up with chewing gum (or, you can <strong>watch this video <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4dDntpb2IiA" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>!)</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><a href="&lt;p%20class=%22p1%22&gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=4dDntpb2IiA&lt;/p&gt;%20&lt;p%20class=%22p2%22&gt;%C2%A0&lt;/p&gt;" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_11.39.15_AM_480x480.png?v=1609779788" alt="" width="527" height="273"></a></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">There are many reasons why we choose to chew gum, and why it’s actually very good for our mental health. Here are some our favourite reasons:</p>
<h3>
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum?page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewing gum</a> helps with focus</h3>
<p class="p1">It has been proven medically, that chewing gum can help us concentrate and become more focused. Well you may ask yourself, why didn’t teachers actually LET US chew gum in school? That’s because it may help the chewer to focus, but it’s distracting for those who are not chewing it!</p>
<p class="p1">The study by Cardiff University showed that participants who chewed gum had quicker reaction times and more accurate results than those who didn’t chew it. Maybe it’s not done on purpose, but since being able to focus makes us feel better, maybe its use is subliminal… so order your bulk gum online through iWholesale Candy and keep chewing!</p>
<p class="p1"><em><strong>Check out some of our most recommended chewing gums [<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>] </strong></em></p>
<p class="p1"><em><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_12.08.14_PM_240x240.png?v=1609780173" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_12.08.00_PM_240x240.png?v=1609780206" alt=""></strong></em></p>
<p class="p1"><em><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_12.07.51_PM_240x240.png?v=1609780226" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_12.07.23_PM_240x240.png?v=1609780246" alt=""></strong></em></p>
<h3 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum?page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewing gum</a> calms the mind</h3>
<p class="p1">Many people who are naturally fidgety claim that chewing gum helps them calm down. Fidgety people can sometimes chew their nails, make clicking sounds with their mouth, tap their feet uncontrollably, or even clench their jaw tight – we even have some fidgeters here at iWholesale Candy, and we remind them to chew gum! The act of chewing – or masticating – <a href="&lt;p%20class=%22p1%22&gt;https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC3158435/&lt;/p&gt;%20&lt;h3%20class=%22p1%22&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">has been proven</a> to lower levels of anxiety and fatigue in many people.</p>
<h3 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum?page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewing gum</a> can help you quit smoking</h3>
<p class="p1">iWholesale Candy has learned that some people smoke because it’s a habit, not necessarily because it’s the nicotine and hundreds of other chemicals calling them out! The habit of holding something in your hand and seeing its smoke releasing, can be quite a soothing feeling for smokers. Well, rather than messing up with your body’s health, why not chew gum instead? Chewing gum has been shown to calm nerves (as previously mentioned) and keep the body and hands busy too.</p>
<h3 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum?page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewing gum</a> for fresh breath, of course!</h3>
<p class="p1">Not just for smokers, but for anyone wishing to have fresh breath for longer than it would take to melt a mint candy, chewing gum is the answer. So yes, this is an obvious answer but as you can see, there are so many more reasons why chewing gum is good for you! </p>
<h3 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum?page=3" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewing gum</a> is just so good!</h3>
<p class="p1">iWarehouse Candy believes that chewing gum means many things to many people: It’s a simple candy you don’t have to indulge in tons of calories for; you can travel with; you can carry with you; you can hide at a meeting and always have fresh breath (we’ve done that too!). Besides, it comes in so many flavours and with various sensations, we just love it – don’t you?</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<h2 class="p1">Marketing takeaway:</h2>
<p class="p1">As a practise, maybe ask your customer how they feel about sharing their thoughts on chewing gum, and why they like it. It will be interesting to learn about your customer, and also give them the opportunity to have a conversation with you. This creates rapport and trust, and will make them feel more connected to buying in your store.</p>
<p class="p1">- - - - </p>
<p class="p1">#iwholesalecandy #candyonline #candywholesale #wholesalecandy #snacksalesonline #buycandyonline #buybulkcandy #ordercandyonline #bestsnacks #candy #onlinecandy #bulkcandy #iwholesale #wholesalesnacks #b2bcandy #sellmorecandy #buymorecandy #marketingideas #howtosellcandy </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-candies-to-relieve-stress</id>
    <published>2021-01-04T11:26:59-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-04T12:19:40-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-candies-to-relieve-stress"/>
    <title>Best Candies to Melt Away Stress</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[This time of year can be stressful as we feel the pressure to accomplish many things. Candy can relieve the stress, and here are some solid methods to show your customer how, using candy:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-candies-to-relieve-stress">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">This time of year can always be stressful. Whether it’s because the Holidays surround so many different tasks and people we need to focus on, or because the New Year brings about mounted stress: The pressure we put on ourselves to accomplish so many new things. At iWholesale Candy, we have some team members who like to have goals set, or “resolutions” and they can sometimes be inspiring, and sometimes be pressure-mounting!</p>
<p class="p1">For whatever the reason that is causing our stress and anxiety, there are some candies we are drawn to as stress relievers – and we all have much of their preference in common:</p>
<h2 class="p1">Chocolate as a stress reliever:</h2>
<p class="p1">Chocolate is not only nutritious, but can be very satisfying to lower stress levels and help us calm down. This is because of the combination of chemical reactions that happen in our brain when eating chocolate: Endorphins, and the release of tryptophan amino acid present in chocolate, linked to the production of serotonin – our “happy feeling” neurotransmitter.</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_11.21.34_AM_240x240.png?v=1609777650" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<p class="p1">So, aside from all the chemical tech talk, chocolate is just so good and satisfying, and the perfect combination of sweet, tart, sometimes salty, that is used to make the best treats. Whether dark, milk or white chocolate, and whether it’s crunchy, chewy, gooey, or melted in cookies, chocolate is by far one of the best stress suppressants there are.</p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_11.06.18_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776592" alt="" width="526" height="287"></p>
<h2 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=chewy*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Chewy candy</a> as stress relievers:</h2>
<p class="p1">At iWholesale Candy, we bet you can almost taste it now: That sensation that is so satisfying… that chewing sensation! Chewing actually sends signals to our brain that something enjoyable has begun to happen, and will be soon digested. When combined with a sweet taste, chewing can bring about some positive feelings (endorphins) to our brain mechanism and nervous system. So go ahead and order all the chewy candy your customers will enjoy, and suggest it to them as stress relievers (great marketing strategy because it’s true!).</p>
<p class="p1">Chewy candies such as Gobstopper Chewy Jawbreakers, Sweetarts Soft &amp; Chewy Ropes, and Hi-Chew Tropical Fruit Chews top our most immediate list of suggested chewy candies.</p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.57.20_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776645" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.57.55_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776667" alt=""></p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.58.42_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776698" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Check our our iWarehouse Candy:<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>[<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=chewy*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">CHEWY</a>]</strong></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<h2 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=sour*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Tangy and Sour candy</a> to relieve stress:</h2>
<p class="p1">This may sound like an unusual suggestion, but it’s true: Sucking on a sour or tangy-tasting candy can be an automatic frame of mind changer. We can go from stress and anxiety to that <em>“WOW!!</em>” feeling within a few seconds – and when it comes to stress, that’s a good thing! Psychiatrists will often suggest things that quickly distract your mind, like listening to music or going outside, and yes, at iWholesale Candy we believe in their suggestion that the power of the tastebuds can be big stress relievers.</p>
<p class="p1">Candies such as Sour Big Chewy Nerds, Warheads Sour Chewy Cubes, and the mouth-puckering Haribo Sour Streamers are some of our suggestions.</p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.57.04_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776827" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.57.13_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776848" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_11.01.34_AM_240x240.png?v=1609776875" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Look at lots more Sour candies<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>[<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=sour*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>]</strong></p>
<p class="p1">The choices you make when you order bulk candy online through iWarehouse Candy, can have a big impact on your sales – but you can also set up the displays to guide your customers to the reasons why they should be buying a particular candy. Whether it’s for enjoyment, as a treat, to have while watching a movie, or in this case, to relieve stress… They will appreciate your guidance! Remember, iWarehouse Candy is here to assist, contact us for guidance and insight, as our team is the most experienced in candy warehouse sales for bulk online orders in Canada.</p>
<p class="p1">- - - -</p>
<p class="p2">#iwholesalecandy #candyonline #candywholesale #wholesalecandy #snacksalesonline #buycandyonline #buybulkcandy #ordercandyonline #bestsnacks #candy #onlinecandy #bulkcandy #iwholesale #wholesalesnacks #b2bcandy #sourcandy #chewycandy #psychologyofcandy #whycandymatters #stressrelief #naturalstressrelief #relievestresswithcandy #candyandstress #chocolate #benefitsofchocolate #chocolatestress</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-rise-in-snack-sales</id>
    <published>2021-01-04T10:31:48-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-04T10:32:55-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-rise-in-snack-sales"/>
    <title>The Rise in Snack Sales</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[We love our snacks! Canada has been ranked 7th in the world-wide snack market – iWholesale Candy takes a look at why we're indulging more than ever:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-rise-in-snack-sales">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">We all enjoy snacking, and especially here in Canada, we ranked seventh in the worldwide snack market. iWholesaleCandy knows we’re impressive snackers who love their sweet and savoury treats, selling over $6.5 billion dollars worth of them.</p>
<p class="p1">This year especially, it almost feels like we “need” our snacks, and sales are showing it – this is why:</p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<h2 class="p1">We’re working from home</h2>
<p class="p1">Challenges for the past year have pushed shops to close down and have their staff work safely from home.</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.30.39_AM_240x240.png?v=1609774267" alt="" width="525" height="317"></p>
<p class="p1">Working from home can make some of us feel more anxious, rather than relaxed, as we adapt to using new technologies, balancing work schedules with family and their respecting spaces. For others it’s the opposite: We’re more relaxed and also may feel more ‘deserving’ so we’re going for the snack department at the local store or market, and indulging in energy bars, salty snacks, crunchy delights and anything that will help satisfy our day (and perhaps make it go by faster?). iWholesaleCandy shares:</p>
<p class="p2">Favourite snacks for working-from-homer's include David’s Sweet &amp; Salty sunflower seeds; Nestlé’s Buncha Crunch Theatre Box snacks; M&amp;M’s Pretzel Chocolate Candies; Andy Capp’s BBQ Fries; and Kit-Kat Duos, such as the Mint + Dark Chocolate bars.</p>
<p class="p2"> <img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_9.57.58_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773630" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_9.58.30_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773649" alt=""></p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_9.59.32_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773672" alt="" width="132" height="214"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.00.26_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773688" alt="" width="194" height="111"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.00.49_AM_100x100.png?v=1609773708" alt="" width="190" height="101"></p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p2"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bulk-candy" target="_blank" title="bulk candy collection" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Look at the HUGE collection of bulk candy we offer! [HERE] </strong></a></p>
<h2 class="p1">We’re busier than ever</h2>
<p class="p1">We’ve become multitaskers who balance work, family, school, and extracurricular activities (whether in person or online). Not only that, but we balance those same things for our spouses and children – plus shopping, cleaning, and hopefully somewhere in between, some sort of respite. This is where snacking comes in: As a pick-me-up and fill-me-up while running around, as a break in the middle of the day, and as an indulgence or ‘stress dessert’ after a wound-up day.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Favourite snacks</strong> for busy folks include filling and satisfying candy bars such as Snickers, Mars, and Reese’s Nutrageous, plus more slow and mellow indulgences like Good &amp; Plenty Licorice candies, and maybe some soothing memory-filled retro candies like Haribo Gold Bears Gummi candy.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/american-chocolate-bars" target="_blank" title="american candy bars" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Check out our favourite American Candy Bars!  [HERE] </strong></a></p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.05.59_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773390" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.06.20_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773409" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.06.53_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773439" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2021-01-04_at_10.08.38_AM_240x240.png?v=1609773466" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1">These are stressful and challenging times, and we all need a break during the day and after, to remind us that YES it’s all worth it! iWholesale candy has definitely experienced a surge in sales, and this is because, as a wholesale candy bulk sale online supplier, we are able to provide insight to the best candies to order online to boost sales in the next few months and beyond.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>Are you feeling the snack sales surge? We’d appreciate your comments below. Why do you think there’s a sales surge in snacks?</strong></p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">- - - -</p>
<p class="p1">#iwholesalecandy #candyonline #candywholesale #wholesalecandy #snacksalesonline #buycandyonline #buybulkcandy #ordercandyonline #bestsnacks #candy #onlinecandy #bulkcandy #iwholesale #wholesalesnacks #b2bcandy #</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/creating-a-store-candy-menu</id>
    <published>2020-12-09T13:54:09-05:00</published>
    <updated>2021-01-04T12:19:18-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/creating-a-store-candy-menu"/>
    <title>Creating a Store &apos;Candy Menu&apos;</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Valentine's Day: It's one of your biggest opportunities to attract a returning customer. iWholesale Candy show you how to set-up a 'Candy Menu' to keep them coming back for more, year 'round.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/creating-a-store-candy-menu">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">With one of the candy industry’s largest celebrations coming up, you’ve got your work cut out for you, and iWholesale Candy is here to help.</p>
<p class="p1">Valentine’s Day is a time for lovers to show their affection through their stomach: Carefully preparing a delicately planned meal, the cocktail to go with it, and then dessert. We all ask ourselves then, <em>what shall I give as a gift?</em></p>
<div style="text-align: left;"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-09_at_1.38.05_PM_240x240.png?v=1607539135" alt="" style="margin-right: 36px; margin-bottom: 12px; float: left;"></div>
<p class="p1"><em>Red, "the colour of love" <br>can be used to entice and<br>remind your customer to buy <br>quickly, as Valentine's Day is approaching!</em></p>
<p class="p1"><em> </em></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">When your customers visits your retail location, they’re probably looking to buy something in particular – whether it be a condiment, fresh bread, or even to satisfy a craving. They have already <em>"something in mind"</em>. This is the opportunity for you to remind your customer that Valentine’s Day is coming up, and the time for them to buy the new, or nostalgic, or specialty candies they’re forgetting they need.</p>
<p class="p2">Displaying candies, chocolates, snacks, and treats, is no longer a matter of just ‘leaving it in the box and hope they see it’ – the 21st century customer is a savvy customer, and they’re also short on time. <em>Ask yourself, when’s the last time you took 30 minutes to buy candy?</em> Maybe never. Your customer responds to this type of shopping in the same manner: Get in, pick up a box of chocolates, get out, move on. <strong>iWholesale Candy has a better marketing and sales strategy for your business:</strong></p>
<h2 class="p1">Enter the ‘Candy Menu’</h2>
<p class="p1">This means the customer’s feeling must be the same as when they enter a restaurant and receive their menu, which lists:</p>
<ol>
<li>
<strong>Their favourites –</strong> what they usually see and buy, and have loved for years.</li>
<li>
<strong>Their quick pick-me-ups –</strong> Something small, yet satisfying .</li>
<li>
<strong>Their comfort foods –</strong> Not what they would normally order, but what they would choose if their needs are to be satisfied: Maybe they had a family reunion that went bad, or they broke up with a significant other.</li>
<li>
<strong>Their intrigues –</strong> The items they’ve seen and are curious to try.</li>
<li>
<strong>The novelties –</strong> The ‘hey, I haven’t seen this before?’ items.</li>
</ol>
<p class="p1">The same goes for the candy they will purchase, and it’s up to the retailer to create the ‘menu’ comprised of each of these 5 items mixed with eachother or provided in sections, to peek their interest and keep them coming back for more. Your customer must see that you’re providing the usual items they have become accustomed to seeing PLUS the new and exciting ones.</p>
<h2 class="p2">Move it around</h2>
<p class="p1">This pattern is changed up and moved around seasonally and is also dependent upon special holidays and celebrations. For example, you can set up a unique ‘summer time’ display, complete with summer-geared POP, balloons and signage, and colourful store dress-up items in yellows, oranges, and light greens. For spring-time, the colours would change and the new arrival of flowers, beach-scenes and cottage getaways would be accented with new candy and Easter celebrations. This technique keeps the customer interested, and it also accentuates the fact your store is “looked after” – cleaned, interesting, and deliciously updated!</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-09_at_1.32.28_PM_480x480.png?v=1607538931" alt="" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;"></p>
<div class="p1" style="text-align: center;"><em>Take a look at the scheme of bright colours in the photo above – doesn't it scream "summer candy"?</em></div>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1">Your customer may be busier now, more than ever, but it doesn’t mean they have to walk in and out in two-minutes. The longer you keep them looking through and finding novelties, the more you tug at their heart strings and peak their curiosity, the more they are probably going to spend with you and continue coming back for more.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>With Valentine's Day fast approaching, now is the time to experiment with colourful displays of red, pink, white and light yellow, to convey the feeling of love and warmth... And have the candy reflect the same! </strong></p>
<p class="p1">- - - -</p>
<p class="p1"><em>At iWholesale Candy we offer the freshest candy wholesale across Canada. We ship fast to you, and take pride in our customer service! Contact us today for all your wholesale candy needs.</em></p>
<p class="p2"> </p>
<p class="p1">#iWholesaleCandy #wholesaleCandyOnline #buyCandyOnline #candyshipping #ordercandyonline #b2bcandy #wholesaleincanada #retailmarketingideas #storedisplay #candydisplay #sellcandy</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/colour-displays-affect-buying</id>
    <published>2020-12-03T12:51:39-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-12-03T12:51:39-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/colour-displays-affect-buying"/>
    <title>Colours Affect Buying Trends</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Colour psychology has been studied for decades. A particular colour display can entice your customer to buy more. Here's why:<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/colour-displays-affect-buying">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">Colour psychology has been studied for decades. A particular colour can make you feel relaxed, excited, even hungry! At iWholesale Candy, we believe colour is one of the most important aspects of setting up your retail outlet – with colours in mind, not just layout, traffic flow, decorations and seasonal signage.</p>
<p class="p1">When a customer walks into a store, they are typically going because they have something already in mind they need: That’s their target. However, we all know that they will almost always walk out with more than one item – either due to a craving they have while in the store, a special sale they’ve seen, or because they thought of someone who would like/need that item. But did you know that a colour display can also make them purchase an item?</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.43.40_PM_480x480.png?v=1607017451" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1">The same thing is done with company logos: Red is the most widely used logo for food companies, while yellow and orange can make you feel hungry. As we all know, red is the colour associated with passion, love, romance, emotions… so when the colours red and yellow are combined, we automatically think of HUNGER, food, want! Can you think of a food chain of companies that uses these colours in their logo?</p>
<p class="p1">Now is the time to be setting up your candy displays for Valentine’s Day – one of the biggest days for people to buy candies, chocolates, and treats. Studies have shown this buying spree is related to love and romance, of course, but also because of the colours! (Remember, red + feelings of hunger = buying). What better than to order your wholesale candy online now, through iWholesaleCandy.ca ? It’s not too early, and it’s never too late. </p>
<p class="p1">We all know the value of setting up check-out displays and POP’s, correct? This is where the consumer will wait in line (especially now, as line-ups tend to be longer) and realize they need a breath-mind, a stick of gum, or something hardier like a chocolate bar.</p>
<p class="p1">Begin displaying red signs, with pink and red bows, balloons, and of course, candy and chocolates nearby. If you must DIY (do it yourself), write your own signs carefully on a red piece of cardboard with black marker, reminding your customer to “Make them feel loved” and buy their special someone a little extra for when they get home. There’s nothing wrong with a little nudge here or there to entice your customer to buy from you – it’s BUSINESS, and iWholesale Candy is here to support your online candy orders as needed.</p>
<p class="p1">The makers of Exberry food colouring, GMT, is predicting that red will will be the top food and beverage colour for 2021. “Red epitomizes human vitality, creating energy, passion and positive action,” says Maartje Hendrickx, GNT’s market development manager, adding that red brings excitement to food and drink products. All colours point to red for 2021!</p>
<p class="p1">After a challenging year, we could all use a little more excitement, gratification, and of course, love. Choose the following candy bulk items to bring more excitement to this next Valentine’s Day:</p>
<h2 class="p1">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/kool-aid-drink-mix" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Kool-Aid drink mixes</a>:</h2>
<p class="p1">Remind them of good times past, with a little excitement! It’s a tasty product they’ll truly consider a treat! Plus, look how nice these orange and red-themed packages look! Check out all the Kool-Aid varieties <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/kool-aid-drink-mix" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[HERE]</strong></a> </p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.06.57_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016310" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.07.01_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016331" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.07.05_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016350" alt=""></p>
<h2 class="p1"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/hi-chew-fruit-chews" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hi-Chew Fruit Chews Candy</a></h2>
<p class="p1">Take them abroad to something they may never have tasted before and would find exotic, like these fruit chews from Japan! There are over 13 types of flavour and colours to choose from, see them <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/hi-chew-fruit-chews" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[HERE]</strong></a>.</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.08.33_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016460" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.08.37_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016557" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<h2 class="p2"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">All things ‘new’… orange and RED! </a></h2>
<p class="p2">If you’re not dressing up your retail outlet with these new items, you’re missing out on finding a loyal customer that’ll keep coming back because you have "ALL THE COOL NEW STUFF"! Check out all our new candy you must have, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[HERE]</strong></a></p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.10.44_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016578" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.10.49_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016673" alt=""></p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.11.21_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016698" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.11.48_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016721" alt=""></p>
<p class="p2"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.12.18_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016742" alt=""><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-12-03_at_12.10.58_PM_240x240.png?v=1607016760" alt=""></p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<h2 class="p2"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=red*%20candy*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">All things RED! </a></h2>
<p class="p2">Once you decide to dress up in red (the store, that is!) then check out iWholesale Candy’s search feature by colour. Type in RED and voila, you will see the large selection of red candies you can buy online! Try it <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/search?q=red*%20candy*" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>[HERE]</strong></a>.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<p class="p1"><strong>What do you think about the colour red? Have you focused on selling candy by colour before? Share your comments with us below... unless you're too hungry?</strong></p>
<p class="p2">- - - -</p>
<p class="p1">#iWholesaleCandy #buyWholesaleCandy #b2bcandy #candyonline #orderCandyBulk #BulkCandy #orderchocolateonline #wintercandy #valentinesDayCandy #wholesalecandyCanada #canadaCandyOnline #wheretobuywholesaleCandy #wholesalecandyonline #warehouseofcandy #retailCandyFavourites #buycheapcandyonline #candyWholesalePrice #buycandy</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/why-your-customers-need-chocolate-this-winter</id>
    <published>2020-11-16T16:15:11-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-16T16:15:42-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/why-your-customers-need-chocolate-this-winter"/>
    <title>Why Your Customers Need Chocolate This Winter</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Let's face it: This has been a challenging year for many of us. Chocolate can provide the satisfaction your customer is looking for; here's why.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/why-your-customers-need-chocolate-this-winter">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">Let’s face it: It has been a challenging year, and we’re all looking for that special something to make us feel content and nurtured. Maybe not everyone is <em>specifically</em> or <em>actively</em> looking for chocolate, but we need something to make us smile and feel happy.</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-16_at_4.04.52_PM_480x480.png?v=1605560712" alt="" width="531" height="321"></p>
<p class="p1">We know chocolate is sweet, satisfying and delicious, however, it’s much more than that. Not just in flavour, but what they’re filled with and even how they’re packaged can be a game-changer. Chocolate is like your customer: No two bars, bits, or bites are the same. Chocolate is nostalgic, memorable, satisfying. It makes us feel comforted, makes us think of the holidays, of having a cup of cocoa after a walk outside, or after skiing. Chocolate is Christmas, is a birthday cake, is a bite of happiness!<br><br>Some of your customers may find they need the ‘reward’ after a long day of working, and they will fit into that 28% of Canadians who consume it daily. Others, need just that bite after lunch or dinner, signifying the end of a meal – something that reminds them of their childhood years when Mom used to give them dessert after Sunday night supper. There are many reasons why they subconsciously think they need chocolate, and these reasons are valid!<br><br>There’s a whole psychology behind eating chocolate, and it has long been the focus of many studies. For example, the study published by the Archives of Internal Medicine shows that it’s possible to eat chocolate and weigh less if you consume small amounts of it at least five times per week. For older customers, it may be the studies that indicated consuming chocolate could help lower the risk of developing heart disease by one-third. Yes, chocolate has been studied and found guilty of rewarding us with feelings of happiness and satisfaction.</p>
<p class="p1"> </p>
<h2 class="p1">Why is it needed during the winter months though?</h2>
<p class="p1">Our bodies don’t produce Vitamin D on their own. Vitamin D plays a big role in growth and development, as well as mood balance, and during winter months when we’re more likely to spend most of our time indoors, a deficiency in Vitamin D can cause the well-studied ‘<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Seasonal_affective_disorder" target="_blank" title="SAD winter blues" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>SAD</strong></a>’ deficiency (Seasonal Affective Disorder). SAD, or ‘Winter Blues’ can be remedied by spending 10 minutes directly under the powerful sunshine rays – but how many of us have enough skin exposed to the sunshine during winter months?<br><br>Enter chocolate, with its <a href="https://speciality.medicaldialogues.in/dark-chocolate-a-rich-and-tasty-source-of-vitamin-d" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>significant amounts of Vitamin D2</strong></a> – especially dark chocolate, followed by milk chocolate, according to scientists at Martin Luther University. Although it may be a long time before your doctor actually prescribes a serving of dark chocolate M&amp;M’s (wouldn't that be nice?) this is a powerful selling factor for your store and a way of reaching customers to give them what their bodies are naturally asking for during winter months. And what better for a retail store than to be able to order it online at wholesale prices?</p>
<p class="p1">According to <a href="https://www.statista.com/topics/4061/chocolate-in-canada/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Statista</strong></a>, consumption of chocolate is on the rise globally, and Canada is no exception, with some of the biggest players including Hershey Company, Nestlé Group, and Lindt &amp; Sprüngli. As we approach the busiest chocolate-sale seasons and holidays – including Christmas and New Year, as well as Valentine’s Day and Mother’s Day in early spring, it’s wise to take a look at your store’s chocolate display and redesign to satisfy this boost in sales. Perhaps set the ice cream and candy aside, and bring on the chocolate displays, such as it’s done in supermarkets.<br><br>This fast-approaching Holiday season will be different than others, for many reasons. Many people will not be travelling to see families, having work parties or hosting get-togethers, so we need to be mindful of ways to continue to keep their adjusting needs satisfied. Stock up on the most beloved traditional chocolates, and also include others which they may not have heard of before, like the New Arrivals of Goetze’s sweet chocolatey Cow Tales Chocolate Brownie Candy, Reese’s Take 5 with its blend of crunchy peanuts, creamy and luscious caramel and crunchy pretzels, or the new M&amp;M’s Fudge Brownie Chocolate Candies with their chewy brownie centre.<br><br><strong>See iWarehouseCandy.ca newest arrivals <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>.</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-16_at_3.27.44_PM_480x480.png?v=1605560358" alt="" width="200" height="145"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-16_at_3.27.51_PM_480x480.png?v=1605560385" alt="" width="144" height="221"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-16_at_3.30.06_PM_480x480.png?v=1605560411" alt="" width="182" height="102"></strong></p>
<h2 class="p1">“Can my store make a difference?” </h2>
<p class="p1">At iWarehouseCandy.ca we believe one store, every store, can make a difference. Humans are creatures of habit, and they have become accustomed to visiting your store and knowing where all items are displayed. They are loyal to you and will continue to come back, as long as you’re providing them with what they need and not sending them elsewhere to find it.<br><br>As your customer looks for ways to prevent winter blues and satisfy the nostalgic traditions of the season, don’t forget the big role chocolate plays. At iWarehouseCandy.ca we’re here to assist you in making sure your store is up to date with the latest stock. Call our team of experts today and order online in bulk, at wholesale pricing, with the best selection.</p>
<p class="p1"><strong>What do you think? Have you ever felt 'cheered up' by having a chocolate treat given to you? Share in the comments below.</strong><br><br>- - - -<br>#orderchocolateonline #chocolateonlinecanada #winterblues #iwarehousecandy #wholesalecandycanada #bulkcandy #candyfavourites #canadiancandyonline #retailcandysales #confectionerywholesalers</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-role-of-candy-for-a-holiday-any-holiday</id>
    <published>2020-11-09T13:26:57-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-11-09T13:27:43-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-role-of-candy-for-a-holiday-any-holiday"/>
    <title>The Role of Candy on a Holiday (Any Holiday)</title>
    <author>
      <name>Suzanne SD</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[A Holiday signifies celebration – whether Christmas, Easter, or even for Labour Day. Adjust your displays and order your wholesale candy purchases accordingly to maximize profit.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-role-of-candy-for-a-holiday-any-holiday">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="p1">Here in Canada, as it is for much of the world, there is no doubt that a Holiday signifies celebration. Whether for Christmas season, Valentine’s Day, or even for Canada Day, your customer is looking for sweet treats to celebrate, and <strong>iWholesaleCandy.ca is here to support with your wholesale candy in Canada.</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-09_at_1.19.50_PM_480x480.png?v=1604946006" alt="candy store" width="529" height="348"></p>
<p class="p1">The seasons change, and accordingly, so do customers’ preferences – for example, customers are attracted to the Cadbury Egg when Easter-time rolls around, as much as seeing the iconic package of Lifesavers Candy Holiday Storybooks <strong>as soon as Fall begins</strong>, signifying Christmas gift-giving season has begun.</p>
<p class="p1">It’s up to retailers to adjust their wholesale candy stock in order to attract purchasing interest. This will keep your customers coming back to see “what’s new”, as well as to pick up their favourites. Display and layout plays a big role in the success of your candy sales, and it’s important to modify your store’s colour scheme to signify a new celebration is coming.</p>
<p class="p1"><a href="https://www.statista.com/statistics/736979/frequency-candy-consumption-in-canada/" target="_blank" title="stats" rel="noopener noreferrer">Statistics show</a> that 40% of Canadians consume candy at <strong>least three times per week,</strong> while 28% will unwrap a sweet treat <strong>daily</strong>. That’s a lot of candy, a lot of candy shopping, and a good opportunity to profit at key times when the consumer is looking to spend.</p>
<p class="p1">For many retailers, 2020 has signified a decrease in sales of many items, from clothing to sporting goods, from shoes to makeup sales, however candy makes the list of items they are not willing to give up on. Customers are looking for treats, special gifts to cheer others up, easy purchases or “no-brainers”, something-candy for everyone, and comforts in general – all of which candy plays a big role in. The time to spruce up candy sales is now and constant, regardless of the holiday that is approaching, and there are many new items they have probably not heard of yet.</p>
<p class="p1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/Screen_Shot_2020-11-09_at_1.07.12_PM_480x480.png?v=1604945250" alt="WHATS NEW iWholesaleCandy" width="522" height="370"></p>
<p class="p1">A steady supply of customer’s favourites is a must, combined with new items such as the <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/twix-cookies-creme-20-ct" target="_blank" title="twix cookies creme" rel="noopener noreferrer">Twix Cookies &amp; Creme</a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/kit-kat-duos-mint-dark-chocolate-bars-24-ct" target="_blank" title="kitkat duos" rel="noopener noreferrer">KitKat Duos Mint &amp; Dark Chocolate</a> or <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/kit-kat-apple-pie-24ct" target="_blank" title="kit kat apple pie" rel="noopener noreferrer">Apple Pie flavours</a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/cow-tales-chocolate-brownie-candy-36-ct" target="_blank" title="cow tales brownie" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cow Tales Chocolate Brownie</a> Candy by Goetze’s, and one of the all-time favourites, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy/products/m-ms-peanut-chocolate-candies-theater-boxes-12ct" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">M&amp;M’s</a> in their new Peanut Butter Chocolate Candies, wrapped up in the convenient Theatre Box.<strong> iWholesaleCandy.ca has got them all for you, check out the latest <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/new-candy" target="_blank" title="new candy 2020" rel="noopener noreferrer">HERE</a>.</strong></p>
<p class="p1"><strong>When’s the best time to order your supply for Valentine’s Day?</strong> Plan ahead, don’t fall short, order quickly, order NOW.<span class="Apple-converted-space">  </span>Our team of candy experts is standing by to help you profit this coming Holiday season, and every holiday here forward.</p>
<p class="p1">- - - -</p>
<p class="p1">#HolidayCandy #BestHolidayCandy #FavouriteCandy #iWholesaleCandy #BulkCandy #BulkCandyInCanada #CandyOnline #BuyCandyInBulk #CanadianOnlineCandy #CandyCrush</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-15-best-selling-candy-bars</id>
    <published>2020-01-10T19:11:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-01-13T13:34:25-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-15-best-selling-candy-bars"/>
    <title>Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars</title>
    <author>
      <name>Billy Wonka</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Candy Bars come and go but there are some that remain our ultimate favourites! There are some with nuts, others that boast caramel, and some even include wafers, the choices seem endless! But with so many to choose from how do you know if your store has what the masses are craving? </span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-15-best-selling-candy-bars">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2><span>Your customers are craving these candy bars!</span></h2>
<p><span>Candy Bars come and go but there are some that remain our ultimate favourites! There are some with nuts, others that boast caramel, and some even include wafers, the choices seem endless! But with so many to choose from how do you know if your store has what the masses are craving? </span></p>
<div>That's where we come in, we want to make sure your candy section is filled with the top-selling Candy Bars. Get ready, this list will make your mouth water and you may even possibly find yourself drooling!</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Here are our 15 Top Best Selling Candy Bars...</strong></div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. Snickers Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/snickers-bar-top-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578703637" alt="Snickers Bar-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>What other Candy Bar could be so delicious and so very satisfying but a Snickers Bar! This old fashioned Candy Bar dates back to 1930! The Snickers Candy Bar is filled with thick, fluffy nougat, perfectly roasted peanuts and creamy caramel, and of course, are all beautifully covered in a generous helping of Milk Chocolate. Each ingredient is evenly dispersed throughout the bar so you get a taste of it all in one magical bite, and can feel the texture of everything that makes this bar so utterly fantastic! </div>
<div>The Snickers Candy Bar may be an old fashioned treat, but Snickers pulls in $2 Billion annually in sales! It's a classic candy bar that's most definitely here to stay! It's the top-selling candy bar around the world! </div>
<div>Over the years there have been over 30 variations of the bar but of course, the original is quintessential for every chocolate section! Fun fact: The Snickers Candy Bar is named after a racehorse that Frank Mars and his family-owned.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. Reese's Peanut Butter Cups</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/reeses-peanut-butter-cups-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578703857" alt="Reese's Peanut Butter Cups-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Technically not in the shape of a bar, but none the less, Reese's Peanut Butter Cups are a top-selling confection! With the most perfect bite of chocolate and peanut butter, there is just the right amount of mild saltiness and sweetness to truly enhance this peanut butter- chocolate, match made in candy heaven!  </div>
<div>This very delectable duo was introduced to us in 1928 H.B Reese, who by the way was an employee of Milton S. Hershey (yes, that guy) at the time.No drama though, as H.B Reese only used Hershey's Chocolate for his delicious candy creations. Upon his sweet candy design, he had no idea that he had created one of the sweetest masterpieces ever to grace a store shelf! Reese's Peanut Butter Cups come in many variations, like dark chocolate, white chocolate and the original milk chocolate. There are plenty to choose from, candy bars and the loved stuffed cups! Check out our Reese's collection for the whole fantastic array and give your customers the classic taste of Reese's Peanut Butter Cups!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/butterfinger-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Butterfinger Candy Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">Butterfinger Candy Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/butterfinger-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578704216" alt="Butterfinger Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Nothing is quite as satisfyingly delicious as the combination of peanuts and chocolate! These two ingredients are food "soul mates" and are always a sweet success in any candy! The Butterfinger Candy Bar is no exception, filled with a distinctive and crispy peanut butter center that is deliciously coated with creamy and rich milk chocolate. The crisp and delightful Butter Finger is an old fashioned candy bar, this sweet darling of a candy bar arrived in 1923! </div>
<div>Butterfinger even had it's sweet Hollywood moment when it was promoted in a film that starred, Shirley Temple. The 1934 movie was called " Take a Bow". But if you're too young to remember that', you might know that it's Bart Simpson's most favourite!</div>
<div>Sweetly satisfy your customers with the peanut butter crunch of the Butterfinger Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4. Twix Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/twix-cookie-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578704797" alt="Twix Cookie Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>This twin candy bar is perfect for sharing! Two fingers of crunchy and buttery tasting biscuit are combined with creamy, golden caramel and surrounded by rich milk chocolate! The Twix Candy bar is a well-loved candy bar all over the world! Twix first got its sweet start in the United Kindom in 1967 and then made it's way to North America in 1979. The name was changed to Twix upon its arrival to North America, in it's beginning, it was known as the Raider Bar. The fun thing about a Twix Candy Bar is you can eat one half now and save the other for later while still getting your chocolate fix! Give your customers their delicious fix, with Twix!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/baby-ruth-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Baby Ruth Candy Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">Baby Ruth Candy Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/baby-ruth-candy-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578705009" alt="Baby Ruth Candy Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>This Candy Bar is a mix of fresh peanuts, smooth caramel and delicious chocolate flavoured nougat that is all bundled up in rich milk chocolate. The Baby Ruth Candy Bar is a substantial candy bar, every bite is packed with tasty texture! Baby Ruth was introduced to a bunch of hungry, sharply dressed flappers in 1921. It proved to be a huge success as soon as it hit the shelves! Many people have speculated that this American Candy Bar was named after Babe Ruth the baseball player but the company claimed that the name Baby Ruth was meant for President Grover Cleveland's daughter, Ruth Cleveland. Whatever the reason behind this delectable candy bar's name it has certainly stood the test of time! It may be an old fashioned candy bar but has millions of satisfied fans almost 100 years later!</div>
<div>Give your customers a sweet taste of the roaring '20s, with the Baby Ruth Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6. Kit Kat Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kit-kat-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578705463" alt="Kit Kat Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>"Have a break, have a Kit Kat" , well at least give your customers a break! The Kit Kat Candy Bar has been around since 1935, it's four crispy wafer-like cookie middle is covered in milk chocolate. This could sound boring to some, but there's something so delicious about this candy bar. Perhaps it is the way those light wafers crunch against your teeth, and the way that rich and creamy, milk chocolate just effortlessly melts on your tongue. The Kit Kat Candy Bar is a stand by bar, much like an old friend that'll never let you down! It's just enough for an afternoon pick me up and it's not overly sweet.</div>
<div> In recent years the Kit kat Candy Bar has gained fans all over the world especially in Japan by adding some very unique and interesting flavours, like green tea, soy sauce, wasabi and sake flavours. If that's just not your thing you can always enjoy the original!</div>
<div>For that famous crisp wafer and chocolate combination they'll love, the Kit Kat Candy Bar is always a winning choice!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/payday-peanut-caramel-bar" target="_blank" title="PayDay Candy Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">PayDay Candy Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/payday-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578708617" alt="Payday Candy Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>A magical thing happens when you add saltiness and sweetness together! The PayDay Candy Bar is a bar that has absolutely no chocolate involved, but don't let that stop you from trying this delicious Candy Bar gem! Inside this bar is a firm, yet chewy, golden caramel center that is generously coated with roasted and salted peanuts. Every bite is more than satisfying with it's sweet and salty combination, as each greatly enhances the other. This American Candy bar is a classic, coming out in 1932 it was a success right from the start!</div>
<div>Get your customers taste buds in a real tizzy, with the old fashion goodness of Payday Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8. Oh Henry Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hersheys-oh-henry-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578709815" alt="Hershey's Oh Henry! Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Give those hungry customers a mouthwatering experience with the delicious candy bar, Oh Henry! This bar is filled with a "big hunk of fudge" in the middle, golden, luscious caramel, full-size crunchy peanuts, covered in a rich coating of milk chocolate. What a satisfying combination! The Oh Henry Candy Bar was introduced to us in 1920, and at that time was called the Tom Henry Bar, until it was changed to what we know today as simply, the Oh Henry. It is rumoured that this candy bar got its name at George Williamson's candy factory. Where a young boy named Henry loved to frequent daily. The group of girls who worked at the factory took a liking to Henry and were forever calling his name out to do errands for them. They say that all across the very large factory is all you could hear were the girls yelling "Oh Henry". Thus, the name seemed fitting! How flattered young Henry must have been!</div>
<div>This Candy Bar is always satisfying, not to mention filling! Give them the old fashioned taste of this peanut, fudge caramel and chocolate filled bar with the delightful deluxe of Oh Henry!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/100-grand-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="100 Grand Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">100 Grand Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/100-grand-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578709982" alt="100 Grand Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Your customers will be feeling extravagant with the delectable, 100 Grand Candy Bar! This American Candy bar includes crispy bits of rice cereal, creamy and golden coloured caramel, and of course, rich milk chocolate. The 100 Grand Candy Bar was introduced to us in 1966. The name is said to have derived from the popularity of game shows that were on television at the time. </div>
<div>This retro candy bar is a very satisfying American bar, not to mention rich! Your customers will be reminded of just how priceless this spectacular candy bar is!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10.Mounds Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/mounds-bars-dark-chocolate-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578710184" alt="Mounds Bar-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Give them a "mound" of deliciousness with the Mounds Candy Bar! This old fashioned candy bar is filled inside with a luscious and chewy coconut middle that is surrounded in a coat of smooth and rich dark chocolate. This American Candy Bar comes in two pieces, so you can eat half now and save the other one for later. Just kidding, we know you'll eat one right after the other! The Mounds Candy Bar is a refreshing change from the usual and makes for a dreamy treat for every coconut lover!</div>
<div>Give them an exotic twist with the impeccable taste of the Mounds Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#11. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/milky-way-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Milky Way Candy Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">Milky Way Candy Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/milky-way-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578874075" alt="Milky Way Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Give those candy craving customers a taste of all things divine, with the Milky Way Candy Bar! With it's out of this world, delectable flavour this American Candy Bar is a deluxe indulgence filled to the max with silky, golden caramel, fluffy, chewy nougat, and rich milk chocolate. This Candy Bar is an old fashioned treat that was introduced in 1923. The Milky Way Candy Bar certainly made important candy history, as it was the very first bar to be filled with other elements other than just plain chocolate. Back in the day, the Milky Way Candy Bar would have set you back a nickel. It was also the biggest candy bar that money could buy, weighing in at 3 oz. , compared to the usual 1.5 oz. Now that's a hefty candy bar!</div>
<div>Show them the way, the Milky Way with this exceptional Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#12. Whatchamacallit Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hersheys-whatchamacallit-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578874315" alt="Hershey's Whatchamacallit Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Your customers will forget what to call this candy bar it's so very delicious! This American Candy Bar is a yummy Candy Bar catch! Filled with crispy peanut butter flavoured rice bits, creamy caramel and coated in a layer of Hershey's milk chocolate! The Whatchamacallit Candy Bar made its delectable debut in 1978 and has been a staple candy bar ever since. Every bite is filled with fantastic chewiness and flavour, it always makes for a satisfying snack! You may have a lapse in memory after eating the Whatchamacallit candy bar, but don't worry it's only temporary! Give them a sweet throwback with this retro Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#13. 5th Avenue Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hersheys-5th-avenue-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578874546" alt="Hershey's 5th Avenue Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>No matter where you are the 5th Avenue candy Bar is always a welcome snack! These Candy bars really are as "rich" as they sound. Your customers will feel sophisticated walking out with this Candy Bar! Inside the 5th Avenue awaits layers of a crunchy peanut butter filling for you to indulge in, while enrobed in milk chocolate. The filling in this Candy Bar is sweet and delightful, with a happy crunch in every bite! 5th Avenue was introduced in 1938 and is still reached for today!</div>
<div>Give them a classy snack with the 5th Avenue Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#14. Heath Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/heath-milk-chocolate-english-toffee-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578874732" alt="Heath Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>This old fashioned candy bar remains a favourite! The Heath Candy Bar is filled with a crispy toffee center that is wrapped in milk chocolate. Meant to resemble "English Toffee" the Heath Bar has a delightful almond-like flavour to it. You might compare this to the Skor Candy Bar, but they really do taste different. The Heath Candy Bar offers that sweet nutty flavour while the Skor Candy Bar is more of a buttery taste. This Candy Bar gives a fantastic crunch in every morsel, with that crunchy texture and deep rich flavour of English Toffee it's a very hard candy bar to pass on. Since 1928, the Heath Candy Bar has satisfied the masses! This Candy Bar is also ideal for topping desserts, break it up into tiny pieces and add it on top of cupcakes, cakes, ice cream or cheesecake. </div>
<div>Make their mouths water with sweet anticipation with the Heath Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#15. M&amp;M's Candies</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/m-m-s-chocolate-candies-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578874994" alt="M&amp;M's Chocolate Candies-Top 15 Best Selling Candies"></p>
<div>Okay, we know it's not really in the shape of a bar but it certainly falls into the candy bar category. Your chocolate section would not be complete if it was left without the sweet addition of M&amp;M's! Coming in a multitude of different flavours and textures, this a favourite candy choice worldwide! These brightly candy-coated chocolates are designed for true candy connoisseurs and are guaranteed to delight those tastebuds!  M&amp;M's started to melt in our mouths in 1941, and they haven't stopped since! This old fashioned candy has staying power and an enormous fan base! No matter what your preference, there's sure to be a flavour of M&amp;M's to satisfy your sweet tooth! Check out our whole collection of M&amp;M's Chocolate Candies and give your customers an old fashioned mouthful of pure deliciousness!</div>
<h3>We had to add these epic candy bars!</h3>
<h3><span>#16. Coffee Crisp Bars</span></h3>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/coffee-crisp-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578875263" alt="Coffee Crisp Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></span></p>
<div>Your customers will feel right at home when they see this iconic Canadian Candy Bar! The Coffee Crisp Candy bar always tastes like "home sweet home". This old fashioned Candy Bar has been delighting us since 1938. Made with perfectly crisp layers of thin wafers, that hold between them, a creamy coffee confection that's covered in rich milk chocolate. The Coffee Crisp is a light, yet satisfying treat. Let's just say, you'll still have room for your mother's meatloaf after this Canadian Candy Bar! Coffee Crisp is made right here in Toronto, Ontario spreading it's joyous deliciousness to everyone who takes a bite!</div>
<div>Spread the joy of the irresistible taste of the Coffee Crisp Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#17. Big Turk Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/nestle-big-turk-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578875551" alt="Nestle Big Turk Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Let's face it, this Canadian Candy bar is a required taste! The Big Turk Candy Bar is a delightfully chewy bar, filled with rose water infused Turkish Delight that is surrounded in a layer of milk chocolate. It's a departure from the typical Candy Bar, it's unique but that just makes it all the more delicious! We may not all agree on the yummy factor of a Big Turk Candy Bar but it's always sure to start a discussion! Love it or hate it, love it or leave it, there is no in-between with this Candy Bar! </div>
<div>The Big Turk Candy Bar is a must-have item for your candy aisle, those who love them, love them well and need to be able to buy copious amounts at any given time! Be uniquely Canadian with the Big Turk! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#18. Eat More Candy Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/eat-more-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578876008" alt="Eat-More Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>With such an inviting name this Canadain Candy Bar will really make you want to eat more! The Eat More candy bar is a delectable tasting candy bar that consists of dark and chewy toffee, with bits of peanuts and chocolate throughout. It's an original candy bar and the texture is ideally chewy! "Dive into the unique" is the slogan for this Candy Bar, but we think it's uniquely delicious! The flavours all work in tandem to make the Eat More such a successful Candy Bar. If you love a candy of great chewiness, the Eat More is it! Sinking your teeth into this Candy Bar would make anyone proud to be Canadian! Always give them more with the Eat More Candy bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#19. Caramilk Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cadbury-caramilk-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578876361" alt="Cadbury Caramilk Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>Give your customers this sweet golden gem, and they'll always be back for more! The Caramilk Candy Bar has been oozing its deliciousness since 1968! Milk Chocolate that is filled with the spectacular sweetness of silky caramel! The Caramilk Candy Bar is nothing short of a luscious candy bar eating experience! We still wonder though, how do they get that caramel inside? It still remains a sweet secret, but one that does sometimes keep us up at night! This Canadian Candy Bar is made right here in Toronto Ontario at the Cadbury Gladstone Chocolate Factory! </div>
<div>Spread the sweet, golden taste with the Carmilk Candy Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#20. Crunchie Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cadbury-crunchie-bars-15-best-selling-candy-bars-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1578876566" alt="Cadbury Crunchie Bars-Top 15 Best Selling Candy Bars"></p>
<div>The Crunchie Bar is sure to have your tastebuds deeply engrossed in a sweet encounter! This Candy bar is made with honeycomb sponge toffee that is covered in Cadbury Milk Chocolate. Each bite is filled with a spectacular "crunch" and the combination of the toffee and chocolate is truly a phenomenal tasting pair. The Crunchie Bar was first made in the UK in 1929, until making it's way to us Canadians in the 1960s. The Crunchie Candy Bar is an original, and definitely stands out in an otherwise crowded sea of nuts, wafers and caramel. </div>
<div>For a truly delectable crunch, give your customers the Crunchie bar!</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Make your Candy Bar section better than average, make it truly incredible with our sweet selection of Candy Bars! Your customers won't bite the hand that feeds them their most favourite Candy Bars!</strong></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/treat-your-customers-royally-with-british-candy</id>
    <published>2019-10-14T08:11:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-10-14T09:05:23-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/treat-your-customers-royally-with-british-candy"/>
    <title>Treat Your Customers Royally with British Candy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Give your customers the " Royal Treatment" with our top-selling British Candy! By offering your customers delicious British Candy you'll be their go-to store for their British Candy cravings</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/treat-your-customers-royally-with-british-candy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2><span>All the Best British Candy and Chocolate!</span></h2>
<p><span><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/treat-your-customers-royally-with-british-candy-confections-chocolate-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1571054969" alt="Treat your Customers Royally with British Candy, Confectionery and Chocolates"></span></p>
<p><span>Give your customers the " Royal Treatment" with our top-selling British Candy! British Confections have an international appeal, and in recent years have gained a dedicated following. By offering your customers delicious British Candy you'll be their go-to store for their British Candy cravings!</span></p>
<div></div>
<div>Here is our best selling British Candy...</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/love-hearts" target="_blank" title="Love Hearts Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Love Hearts Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/swizzels-love-hearts-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571024987" alt="Swizzels Love Hearts British Candy"></p>
<div>Love Hearts Candy is an old fashioned candy that has been loved since 1954. This British confection consists of pretty pastel-coloured, tablet-like candies that come in a roll. Love Hearts candies not only offer their great fruity and fizzy taste, but each candy is also inscribed with a message of love! It's a double hit of sweetness! With phrases such as "only you", "true love" and "kiss me" your customers will surely be feeling the love! This British confection is filled with sweet deliciousness and romance! Share the love with Love Hearts Candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/nestle-lion-bar-uk-36-ct" target="_blank" title="Nestle Lion Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nestle Lion Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/nestle-lion-bars-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571025279" alt="Nestle Lion Bars British Candy "></p>
<div>You could have a sweet safari right in your store with this delectable tasting British Chocolate Bar! The Nestle Lion Bar is a satisfying British Candy bar that is made with crispy wafers, creamy and sweet caramel, and crisp pieces of cereal that are then covered with a helping of Nestle Milk Chocolate! You really will want to roar after indulging in this delicious Lion Bar! Coming out in 1976, this British Confection makes a perfect snack! Be " king of the jungle" in your candy store with the Nestle Lion Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/walkers-nonsuch-original-toffee-bars-10-ct" target="_blank" title="Walkers Nonsuch Original Toffee Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer">Walkers Nonsuch Original Toffee Bars</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/walkers-nonsuch-toffee-bars-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571025514" alt="Walker's Nonsuch Original Toffee Bars British Candy"></p>
<div>The Walkers NonSuch Original Toffee Bars are a delicious British Candy that has been loved for over 100 years! Choose from many different flavours of Walkers Nonsuch Toffee Bars or wrapped candy form. Each delectable piece of any Walkers Toffee is made with the finest ingredients so you can give your customers the very best! This British Candy is famous all over the world and well known for its impeccable taste, variety of different flavours and it's perfect Toffee texture! The Walkers Toffee is a must-have British Confection for your British Cany section!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/cadbury-flake-bars-uk-24-ct" target="_blank" title="Cadbury Flake Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cadbury Flake Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cadbury-flake-bars-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571025816" alt="Cadbury Flake Bars British Candy"></p>
<div>Help your customers discover why this delectable British Candy is really called Flake! The Cadbury Flake Bar is a delicate and very light textured chocolate that will delightfully melt perfectly in your mouth. You could experience those little awesome"Flakes" upon biting into a Flake Bar, but that's just part of the joy of indulging in this exquisite British Confection! Made with an irresistible tasting milk chocolate, it's airy and light texture makes the Cadbury Flake Bar a pure winner! </div>
<div>Let those sweet "Flakes" of supreme yumminess fall right into your customer's mouths! Be sure to stock this brilliant tasting British Cadbury Flake Bar in your candy aisles!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/funny-money-edible-paper-money-24-packs" target="_blank" title="Funny Money" rel="noopener noreferrer">Funny Money</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/funny-money-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571026173" alt="Funny Money British Candy"></p>
<div>It might not grow on trees, but our British friends think you should be able to eat it! Funny Money is an amusing British Confection that is made out of edible rice paper and resembles European money. Coming in an array of colours and denominations, make this a fun British Candy to share with your friends or have at a party, maybe even a poker game! So go on and put your money where your mouth is with this entertaining and yummy Funny Money!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/frys-turkish-delight-uk" target="_blank" title="Fry's Turkish Delight" rel="noopener noreferrer">Fry's Turkish Delight</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/frys-turkish-delight-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571026370" alt="Fry's Turkish Delight British Candy"></p>
<div>Delight your customers with the delicious and unique taste of Fry's Turkish Delight! This British confection has been loved since 1914. It's a classic and sophisticated taste of chocolate-covered Turkish Delight. With its fragrant, rose water infused middle each bite is luscious and tender and of course, filled with "Eastern Promise". This old fashioned candy has an amazing and distinctive taste. It's a refreshing change from the usual candy bar. Invite your customers to be sweetly delighted with this old fashioned chocolate treat, this is one  British Candy you don't want to miss!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/cadbury-curly-wurly" target="_blank" title="Cadbury Curly Wurly" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cadbury Curly Wurly</a>
</h3>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cadbury-curly-wurly-chocolate-bars-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571056810" alt="Cadbury Curly Wurly British Chocolate Bars"></p>
<div>Your customers will love this retro chocolate bar! The Cadbury Curly Wurly is a delectable British Chocolate Bar. With Its exquisite strands of chewy caramel and delicious milk chocolate braided together, to create a very harmonious chocolate-eating experience! The Curly Wurly made its debut during the 1970s and remains a popular and well-loved chocolate bar to this day! This famous British confection has been called by other names in the past like "Wig Wag" and "Marathon", but whatever you might call this bar, it truly stands out as an exceptional British Chocolate Bar! Cadbury Curly Wurly is one of many spectacular tasting British Cadbury Chocolate Bars. Give your customers an authenticly sweet BritishCandy experience with the entire line of Cadbury Chocolate Bars!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/millions-apple-tubes-uk-12-ct" target="_blank" title="Millions Candy Tubes" rel="noopener noreferrer">Millions Candy Tubes</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/millions-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571024680" alt="Millions British Candy"></p>
<div>This British Candy is one in a "million"! The Millions Tubes are a unique British Candy that consists of tiny round balls of candy that are crunchy on the outside and chewy on the inside. Don't let their small size fool you, the Millions Candy might be tiny but they have a big flavour! This fun and flavourful British confection come in an assortment of yummy flavours like Bubblegum, Cola, Apple, Blackcurrant, Strawberry and Rasberry. You're sure to find a favourite flavour among the Millions Candy Tubes, or try them all and mix and match to create a unique taste! Give your customers the yummiest of tiny candies with the Millions Tubes!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. Rowntrees Jelly Tots</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/rowntrees-jelly-tots-british-confectionery-iwholesalecandy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1571057987" alt="Rowntrees Jelly Tots British Confectionery"></p>
<div>Give your customers a soft and chewy taste of this retro British Candy! Jelly Tots are a delicious fruit tasting candy with a distinctively soft and supple jelly texture inside that are perfectly sugar-coated on the outside. You'll love to sink your teeth into the juicy flavours of this candy! Jelly Tots Candy comes in a sweet selection of Blackcurrant, Orange, Strawberry, Lemon and Lime. Made with all-natural colours and flavours this British confection only uses real fruit juice! This fantastic fruity candy was introduced in 1967 and remains a number one candy choice today! For that authentic and refreshing natural fruity taste, give them a British taste with Jelly Tots!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10. Barratt Sherbet Fountain</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/barratt-sherbet-fountain-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571058270" alt="Barratt Sherbet Fountain British Confectionery"></p>
<div>This iconic British Candy came out in 1925! The Sherbet Fountain is sure to "flood" your tastebuds with a taste from the good old days! This old fashioned candy is a tube that is filled with yummy and fizzy sherbet and includes a stick of black licorice to dip inside the sherbet filled tube. The fizzy sherbet and black licorice are a perfect match, each enhancing the taste of the other! There is now new packaging for the Sherbet Fountain, the licorice stick is packed inside the tube for safekeeping! Your customers will love to taste the goodness from this fountain! The Sherbet Fountain Candy is a sweet taste of nostalgia!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#11. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/frisia-flying-saucers-candy-500-count-tub" target="_blank" title="Flying Saucers Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Flying Saucers Candy</a>
</h3>
<div>This candy will take your taste buds on a sweet and faraway journey! The Flying Saucers Candy is made with rice paper and filled inside with a sour-tasting sherbet! The disc shape of this candy does look like a UFO or Flying Saucer, hence the name. This British Candy comes in soft and pretty pastel colours, yellow, pink, green and blue. Flying Saucers came out in the early 1950s and is ranked as one of Britain's top-selling candies! Get your customers ready for this delicious blast from the past with the Flying Saucers Candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#12. Maynards Bassetts Liquorice Allsorts Candy</h3>
<div>A favourite British Candy since 1900! Maynards Bassets Liquorice Allsorts is a black licorice candy that comes with brightly coloured candy additions. This British candy is filled with bold black licorice taste with a chewy and soft texture. Made with all-natural colours and flavours adds to the high-quality taste of this old fashioned candy! Maynards Bassetts Liquorice Allsorts will deliver "all sorts" of supreme British Candy deliciousness to your customers! Please those licorice lovers with this Brilliant British confection!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#13.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/nestle-drifter-uk-48-ct" target="_blank" title=" Nestle Drifter Chocolate Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Nestle Drifter Chocolate Bars</a>
</h3>
<div>This retro British chocolate bar will have you sweetly drifting in a delicious chocolate induced state of bliss! The Nestle Drifter Chocolate Bar is made of two light and airy wafers, covered in golden caramel and all enclosed in delectable Nestle milk chocolate! A bite that is perfectly balanced slightly crisp and sweetly creamy! This delectable British confection was introduced in 1980 and remains a favourite British Chocolate Bar today! Encourage your customers to "drift" away with the irresistible goodness of the Drifter Chocolate Bar!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#14. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/maynards-bassetts-wine-gums-12-ct" target="_blank" title="Maynards Bassetts Wine Gums" rel="noopener noreferrer">Maynards Bassetts Wine Gums</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/maynards-bassetts-wine-gums-british-confectionery-iwholesalecandy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1571056414" alt="Maynards Bassetts Wine Gums British Confectionery"></p>
<p> </p>
<div>The Maynards Bassetts Wine Gums are one of Britain's most famous sweets! This old fashioned British Candy is full of refreshing flavours like Lime, Raspberry, Blackcurrant, Orange and Grapefruit. Made to resemble the sophisticated taste of port, these delicious Wine Gums are meant, of course, to be savoured like fine wine. But don't worry, this British confection contains no alcohol! Their texture is chewy but firm, and each flavour is smooth, fruity and exquisite tasting! Give your customers a classically charming, British taste with Maynards Bassetts Wine Gums!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#15. Fruit-Tella English Fruits</h3>
<div>Invite your customers to experience some exquisite tasting English Fruits with the Fruit-Tella English Fruits Candy! Made with all-natural colours and flavours, and real fruit juices make this an exceptional tasting British Candy! This chewy and juicy tasting candy comes in the flavours of Pear, Apple, Raspberry and Blackberry. This old fashioned candy came out in the 1930s' and has always been sweet hit ever since! Be sure to stock this delicious British candy gem in your candy section, England is just a sweet bite away!</div>
<h3>#16. Dairy Milk Bars</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cadbury-dairy-milk-chocolate-bars-british-candy-iwholesalecandy-toronto.jpg?v=1571055314" alt="Cadbury Dairy Milk Chocolare Bars-British Candy and Confectionery"></p>
<div>
<span>Take your customers away to a blissfully, beautiful chocolatey place with Cadbury Dairy Milk Chocolate Bars! The British Cadbury Dairy Milk Bars are rich, creamy and have the texture of lush velvet. Every British Dairy Milk Chocolate Bar no matter what the flavour, is always more than delectable with its distinctively delicious British taste! This famous British Chocolate is sought after all over the world, and for good reason, it is truly a bar of exceptional tasting chocolate! </span>
<div>Be sure to check out our collection of Cadbury Dairy Milk Chocolate Bars, with many different chocolate bars to choose from, you'll want to taste them all! This sweet British confection will perfectly complete your chocolate section!</div>
<h3>Add British Sweets to your Candy Section</h3>
</div>
<div></div>
<div>Some of the most iconic candy comes from our sweet British friends across the pond! Keep your candy aisles stocked with these treasured British confections, you never know when the craving for British candies will arise! By adding some British treats to your store you'll have the opportunity to attract some new customers and intrigue some of your regulars!</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong> You really can "treat your customers royally" with our sweet selection! Browse our British Candy collection today for some deliciously unique candies and delectable chocolates!</strong></div>
<div style="text-align: center;">
<strong>Cheers</strong>!!!</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/british-candy" target="_blank" title="Check Out All The Best British Candy and Chocolate Here" rel="noopener noreferrer">Check Out All The Best British Candy and Chocolate Here</a></h3>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-halloween-candy</id>
    <published>2019-09-16T22:11:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-10-07T07:48:15-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-halloween-candy"/>
    <title>Top 10 Best Selling Halloween Candy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div>From ghosts and goblins, vampires and witches they all have one thing in common, they love to gobble up Halloween Candy! Get your candy aisles ready for some ghoulish sweetness!</div>
<div>Here is our Top Selling Halloween Candy...</div><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-halloween-candy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2><span>Spooky but Yummy Halloween Candy</span></h2>
<p style="text-align: left;"><img alt="Top 10 Halloween Candy" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_medium.jpg?v=1568686279" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><span>Get your store Halloween ready with our spooktacular Halloween Candy! Trick or treat? Is the question this season and we want to make sure you have all the treats you need! </span></p>
<div>From ghosts and goblins, vampires and witches they all have one thing in common, they love to gobble up Halloween Candy! Get your candy aisles ready for some ghoulish sweetness!</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Here is our Top Selling Halloween Candy...</strong></div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. Candy Corn</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/candy-corn-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1570405742" alt="Candy Corn Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>Love it or hate it, there's something about this time of year that beckons us to eat Candy Corn, or at least try it! This tri-coloured confection is meant to resemble a piece of corn. It has a creamy fondant texture with a sweet and distinctive flavour.</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/candy-corn-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570405892" alt="Candy Corn Halloween Candy at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>This old fashioned candy has been around since the 1880s! The world has loved it, complained about it and of course, happily indulged in this candy kernel! Candy Corn candy has some definite staying power, it's a must-have Halloween candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/vidal-gummi-eye-balls-1-2-kg" target="_blank" title="Gummi Eye Balls" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gummi Eye Balls</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/gummi-eyeballs-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570405098" alt="Gummi Eyeballs Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>We know it sounds a little gross, but that's what Halloween is for! Indulging in some delicious and gruesome candy! That's just what these Gummi Eye Balls offer, a sort of yuckiness that does appeal to certain candy lovers! This scary Eye Ball would make quite a statement in your candy aisle! Imagine browsing the candy and seeing a giant bloodshot eyeball staring back at you! </div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/gummy-eyeballs-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570405176" alt="Vidal Gummi Eye Balls Halloween Candy"></div>
<div>The Gummi Eye Balls Candy is a gummy candy with a chewy and soft texture and comes in the delightful flavour of strawberries and cream. This Halloween Candy would cause quite a stir at your fun Halloween Party! Imagine a tray full of this bulk candy at your Candy Bar or Candy Buffet! Give your customers "a feast for the eye" and their tastebuds!`</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wack-o-wax-wax-fangs" target="_blank" title="Wax Fangs" rel="noopener noreferrer">Wax Fangs</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/wack-o-wax-fangs-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570405397" alt="Wack-O-Wax Fangs Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>Not only is this a tasty wax candy, but you can also actually wear these fangs! Put them on a scare all your customers, or just get them in the mood for Halloween! This old fashioned candy has been eaten and played with for generations!</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/wack-o-wax-fangs-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1570405571" alt="Wack-O-Wax Halloween Candy"></div>
<div>This novelty candy has been around since the 1940s and also comes in a set of oversized red wax lips and also a handsome wax mustache. This candy makes for a fun and amusing Halloween Candy! Entertain your customers with the Wack-O- Wax Candies!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/albanese-large-assorted-fruit-gummi-worms" target="_blank" title="Gummy Worms" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gummy Worms</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/gummy-worms-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570406210" alt="Gummy Worms Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>They might be creepy and crawly, but these worms you'll love to have in your mouth! The Gummy Worm is always a very suitable Halloween candy! It's fun and amusing and of course always super delicious! Choose from Sour Candy Gummy Worms or just simply sweet and fruity.</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/gummy-worms-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1570406270" alt="Gummy Worms Halloween Candy at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>Gummy Worms come in many colours this bulk candy could be used on a candy bar or a spooky Halloween Party. Gummy Worm candy is also an ideal candy for the use of decorating cakes or cupcakes.</div>
<div>Your customers will squirm will sweet satisfaction with our yummy Gummy Worms!</div>
<div> </div>
<h3>#5. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/caramel-apple-pops" target="_blank" title="Caramel Apple Pops" rel="noopener noreferrer">Caramel Apple Pops</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/caramel-apple-pops-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1570406581" alt="Caramel Apple Pops Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>This lollipop has all the rich and delightful flavours of Fall! Caramel Apple Pops are a delectable Halloween Candy! A caramel lollipop on the outside with a vibrant tasting green apple middle. The Caramel Apple Pop is a retro candy that is sure to satisfy those hungry ghosts and goblins or anyone else for that matter!</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/caramel-apple-pops-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_large.jpg?v=1570406639" alt="Tootsie Caramel Apple Pops Halloween Candy"></div>
<div>Give them a delicious tasting lollipop with the Caramel Apple Pops!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/vidal-gummi-hairy-spiders-1-2-kg" target="_blank" title="Gummi Hairy Spiders" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gummi Hairy Spiders</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/vidal-gummi-hairy-spiders-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_large.jpg?v=1570406837" alt="Vidal Gummy Hairy Spiders Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>These Hairy Spiders are sure to deliciously crawl down your throat! Gummi Hairy Spiders might scare off a few, but not the real hardcore candy lovers! This gummy candy makes an ideal Halloween Candy! They may look a little repulsive, but you can rest assured these Spiders are a sweetly superb tasting candy! Filled with a fresh and fruity taste, this amusing bulk candy would be a huge hit at a Halloween Party or displayed in your next candy bar.</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Gummy Hairy Spiders will make your candy section come alive for the fun and frightful Halloween season!</strong></div>
<h3>#7. Kerr's Halloween Kisses</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kerrs-kisses-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_large.jpg?v=1570407240" alt="Kerr's Kisses Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>Who doesn't like a kiss? Especially a soft and flavourful, melt in your mouth molasses kiss! `Kerr's Halloween Kiss is a classic Canadian Candy that goes hand in hand with Halloween! Kerr's Candy sure knows how to make a delicious candy, they've been around since 1895! This old fashioned candy is a staple that is an expected Halloween candy to have when your Canadian! The Kerr's Halloween Kiss comes complete with it's seasonal Halloween looking wrapper, sure to get your customers into some sweet, Halloween cheer! </div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#8. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/huer-jumbo-sour-bones-1-kg" target="_blank" title="Jumbo Sour Bones Gummy Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jumbo Sour Bones Gummy Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/huer-jumbo-sour-bones-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_large.jpg?v=1570447316" alt="Huer Jumbo Sour Bones Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>The bare bones of Halloween candy would, of course, include our Jumbo Sour Bones! This delicious gummy candy is a truly toothsome sour candy! Your customers will love to indulge in these yummy bones. They're always fresh and chewy, with a pucker some sugary coating on the outside. The Jumbo Sour Bones come in a multicoloured bone shape. This bulk candy would be a very entertaining gummy candy to have at your next candy bar, candy buffet, or a frightful Halloween Party! Get your store ready for Halloween with this satisfying sour candy!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#9.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/vidal-gummi-brains-1-kg" target="_blank" title="Gummi Brains" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gummi Brains</a>
</h3>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/vidal-gummi-brains-jelly-filled-gummy-candy-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1570447914" alt="Vidal Gummy Brains Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>Get your brain around Halloween with this scary Halloween candy! The Gummi Brain is a delicious tasting strawberry flavoured gummy candy with a soft jelly-like middle. Yes, a little gory but perfect for Halloween! This bulk candy is sure to sweetly amuse your guests at your next candy buffet or candy bar. These gummy candy brains would make a brilliant statement at a Halloween party! Give your customers the scary  Halloween shivers with these yummy, Gummi  Brains!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#10. Hershey's Miniatures</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hershey-minatures-chocolate-bars-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570448253" alt="Hershey Miniatures Chocolate Bars Halloween Candy"></p>
<div>A mix of miniature Hershey Chocolate Bars is sure to get everyone in the Halloween spirit! This delicious mix of The Hershey's Miniatures includes little snack-size versions of some of your most favourite chocolate bars! Included in this marvellous mix is, Mr. Goodbar, Crispy Krackel, Creamy Hershey's Bar and The Rich Hershey's Dark Chocolate Bar.</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hershey-minatures-chocolate-bars-halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-mississauga_large.jpg?v=1570448368" alt="Hershey Miniatures Chocolate Bars Halloween Candy at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>Don't be fooled by their size, yes these are small but BIG in flavour! Your customers will love some delectable chocolate Halloween candy! </div>
<h3><strong>Have a Truly Sweet and Spectacularly Spooky Halloween!</strong></h3>
<p><strong><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/halloween-candy-i-wholesale-candy-toronto_large.jpg?v=1570448864" alt="Halloween Candy-iWholesaleCandy.ca"></strong></p>
<div><span>Make Halloween sweeter than ever with our yummy and fun Halloween Candy! Take your customers on a trick or treat excursion right inside your very own store! They'll love our creepy crawly sweet spider critters and the dreadful-looking, but disgustingly delicious gummy candy Brains and Eyeballs! Keep all the tasty, hair raising Halloween horror in your candy aisles, and give them a truly sweet and spectacularly spooky Halloween! </span></div>
<div><span></span></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-back-to-school-candies</id>
    <published>2019-08-04T07:05:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-08-17T13:51:49-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-back-to-school-candies"/>
    <title>Best Selling Back To School Candies</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Be sure to be ready for these hungry students!  They'll need some real fuel for learning! Make your store the best part of their school day and have your candy aisles stocked with our best Back To School Candies!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-back-to-school-candies">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2>Back to School is the Sweetest Time of the Year!</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Best Selling Back to School Candies at Wholesale Prices" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/best-selling-back-to-school-candies-wholesale-candy-canada_medium.jpg?v=1564916668" style="float: none;"></p>
<p><span>The time has come! It's inevitable, back to school is upon us! There are those who will drag their feet in sadness just thinking of the impending doom of sitting in a classroom again. Or the all too overly enthusiastic teacher's pet who has spent all Summer brushing up on their math skills. Along with the new shoes, pens, pencils and books, there are brand new backpacks to be filled, with candy of course!</span></p>
<div>Be sure to be ready for these hungry students!  They'll need some real fuel for learning! Make your store the best part of their school day and have your candy aisles stocked with our best Back To School Candies!</div>
<div></div>
<div><strong>Our Best Selling Back To School Candies...</strong></div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/nerds-candy" target="_blank" title="Nerds Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nerds Candy</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Nerds Candy-Best Selling Back to School Candies at Wholesale Prices-iWholesaleCandy.ca" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/best-selling-back-to-school-candy-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565493317" style="float: none;"></p>
<div>A magically delicious Wonka Candy that is although small in size, is mighty in flavour! Nerds Candy come in a dual-chambered box with two different flavours on each side, choose from, Grape and Strawberry, Watermelon and Cherry, Wild Berry and Peach, Surf and Turk, or the Nerds Double Dipped Candy. Eat one side at a time, or create a yummy combination of both sides at once!</div>
<div>Nerds Candy make it easy to share with your BFF! They're also convenient size-wise, easy to throw in a school bag, hide in a desk or even keep in your pocket! Who wouldn't love this retro candy? Makes a great after school pick me up or a candy to share during recess!</div>
<div>Let them know how cool being a "Nerd" is with the tangy and crunchy taste of Nerds Candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-skool-bus?_pos=1&amp;_sid=fce535f0b&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Kidsmania Skool Bus" rel="noopener noreferrer">Kidsmania Skool Bus</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kidsmania-skool-bus-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565493772" alt="Kidsmania Skool Bus-Best Selling Back to School Candies-iWholesaleCandy.ca"></p>
<div>Get your customers excited and amped up for back to school with the Kidsmania Skool Bus! This is a fun and yummy novelty candy that you can not only play with but also enjoy the candy inside!</div>
<div>This eye-catching, brightly coloured yellow school bus comes equipt with lots of candy! The wheels on the bus really do go round and round! Open up the back hatch and a big helping of brightly coloured and crunchy candy will appear! Eat the delicious candy then play with the fun " Skool Bus".</div>
<div>A cute and fun candy addition to have in your candy aisle!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/haribo-alphabet-letters" target="_blank" title="Haribo Alphabet Letters" rel="noopener noreferrer">Haribo Alphabet Letters</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/haribo-alphabet-letters-gummy-candy-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565494227" alt="Haribo Alphabet Letters Gummy Candy"></p>
<div>Help your smallest customers sweetly learn their ABC's with the Haribo Alphabet Letters! This old fashioned gummy candy has been loved since the 1920s, and it's just as delicious today!</div>
<div>Brightly coloured and perfectly chewy, each letter is filled with its own delicious fruity flavour. Coming in five tasty flavours like Pineapple, Lemon, Orange, Raspberry and Strawberry. Be sure to taste every letter! The Haribo Alphabet Letters make learning the alphabet a delightfully sweet adventure!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/efrutti-gummi-candy-lunch-bag-12-ct" target="_blank" title="efrutti Gummi Candy Lunch Bag" rel="noopener noreferrer">efrutti Gummi Candy Lunch Bag</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/efruitti-gummy-candy-lunch-bag-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565494624" alt="efruitti Gummi Candy Lunch Bag "></p>
<div>Lunch was never so sweet! Especially the efruitti Gummi Candy Lunch Bag! This delicious gummy candy has a mini version of lunch but in gummy candy form! Everybody will want to cozy up to you in the lunchroom with this super yummy lunch, which includes, chewy hamburgers, delicious sour french fries, refreshingly sweet cola, a loaded hot dog and even a pizza! This lunch might be miniature in size but it certainly packs some big flavour! </div>
<div>Get your customers really excited about their lunch break, they'll love to feast on this lunch! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/hubba-bubba-bubble-gum" target="_blank" title="Hubba Bubba Bubble Tape Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hubba Bubba Bubble Tape Gum</a><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hubba-bubba-bubble-gum-tape-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565532232" alt="Hubba Bubba Bubble Gum Tape-Best Selling Back to School Candy-iWholesaleCandy.ca">
</h3>
<div>Share with your customers the sweet secret of amazing bubbles with the awesome Hubba Bubba Bubble Tape Gum!</div>
<div>This luscious tasting Bubble Gum is six feet long! That's hard to beat! The Hubba Bubba Bubble Tape Bubblegum is not only juicy, sweet and flavoursome it really does blow some big and beautiful bubbles! Most Bubble Gum comes in wrappers but Hubba Bubba came out with this genius tape dispenser! It's so easy and convenient to carry around, and makes it ideal for sharing! Now you can make every recess bubbly and fun! Just don't stick that disregarded chewed up bubble gum under the desk! Detentions are no fun!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/whatchamacallit-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="Whatchamacallit Candy Bar " rel="noopener noreferrer">Whatchamacallit Candy Bar </a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hershey_s-whatchamacallit-american-candy-bar-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565533273" alt="Hershey's Whatchamacallit American Candy Bars-Best Selling Back to School Candy-iWholesaleCandy.ca"></p>
<div>Sometimes it's hard to come up with the right answer, especially when you are put on the spot in front of all your classmates! That's why we suggest the Whatchamacallit Candy Bar for back to school! Just simply hold up this delicious American candy bar if you are called upon. The best part is you can eat it later! The Whatchamacallit Candy Bar is loaded with crispy peanut butter flavoured rice crisps, along with creamy caramel that is all completely covered in a generous coating of chocolate! A delectable American Candy Bar that is deliciously satisfying! In fact, this candy bar is so delectable you might even forget it's name! </div>
<div>Don't let your hungry customers forget the name of this amazing candy bar, be sure to have it fully stocked in your candy aisle!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/smarties-chocolate-candies-24-ct" target="_blank" title="Smarties Chocolate Candies" rel="noopener noreferrer">Smarties Chocolate Candies</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/nestle-smarties-canadian-candies-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_049ab7c4-8930-428e-949a-fdb37834b1e5_large.jpg?v=1565534329" alt="Nestle Smarties Canadian Candy"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<div>A true Canadian classic candy! Now you can help boost your customer's brainpower with Smarties!  These brightly coloured bits of candy come with the perfect crunch on the outside and are filled with chocolate on the inside. Every round morsel of Smarties Chocolate Candy will make you proud to be Canadian! In the USA they call what we call "Rockets" Smarties Our Smarties are the real deal, they win every time!</div>
<div>You will become a Smartie! Just be consuming them on a regular basis. It's always a smart choice to choose Smarties! Eat them one at a time or dump the entire contents in your mouth at once! Any way you enjoy them, Smarties are a perfect candy anytime!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8. Kidsmania Emoji Lollipop</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kidsmania-emojipops-lollipops-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565535061" alt="Kidsmania EmojiPop Lollipops-Best Selling Back to School Candies-iWholesaleCandy.ca"></p>
<div>Now you can help your customers be more expressive! It's easy with these fun-filled Emoji Lollipops from Kidsmania. Not only are these fruity and delicious tasting lollipops they also include a laser light inside so you can light up each Emoji face!  Help your customers to LOL with this yummy and fun treat from Kidsmania! The Emoji Lollipop is not your average Lollipop it also includes fun and entertainment! Light up the world with a sweet and happy face and eat a delicious lollipop!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/vidal-gummi-brains-1-kg" target="_blank" title="Vidal Filled Gummy Brains" rel="noopener noreferrer">Vidal Filled Gummy Brains</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/vidal-gummi-brains-jelly-filled-candies-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565537235" alt="Vidal Jelly-Filled-Gummy-Candy-Best-Selling-Back-to-School-Candies-iWholesaleCandy.ca"></p>
<div>Show your customers how to become a sweet brainiac with these delicious Vidal Filled Gummy Brains! Made to resemble a real brain! Soft and chewy flavourful candy with a strawberry flavoured outside and a yummy jelly-filled centre.Great for a science project, or a spooky candy for Halloween! Some people might think that they're gross but that just means more for you! Gummy Brain Candy is not only delightfully delicious but also very amusing! Rumour has it that Hannibal Lecter loved these! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/mega-double-lollies" target="_blank" title="Smarties Mega Lollies" rel="noopener noreferrer">Smarties Mega Lollies</a>
</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/smarties-mega-lollies-lollipops-retro-candy-best-selling-back-to-school-candies-iwholesalecandy_large.jpg?v=1565537692" alt="Smarties Mega Lollies Lollipops Retro Candy"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<div>Teach those kids all about the good old days with this American retro candy! The Smarties Mega Lollies is the perfect balance of tart and sweet! This retro lollipop tastes just like the American version of Smarties, or what we call "rockets" in Canada.</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/smarties-mega-lollies-lollipops-iwholesalecandy.ca_large.jpg?v=1565538006" alt="Smarties Mega Lollies Lollipops"></div>
<div>You can even bite through this lollipop as it's made in a tablet-like texture. Great for on the go students, teachers too! Give your customers a sweet afternoon pick me up with  Mega flavour with the classic Smarties Mega Lollies!</div>
<h3>Make Back to School $weeter</h3>
<p><strong>Send them all back to school sweetly with our delicious and exciting selection of wholesale candy! Make your store a popular and fun place with the addition of bubble gum, lollipops, gummy candy, and so much more! </strong></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-summertime-candy</id>
    <published>2019-07-10T22:51:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-07-13T21:46:04-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-summertime-candy"/>
    <title>Best Selling Summertime Candy</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div>Be sure your candy store is Summer ready! Fill your candy aisles with the sweet taste of Summer! Here is some of our Best Selling Summertime Candy...</div><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/best-selling-summertime-candy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;">Summer + Candy = $weet Times!</h2>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/best-selling-summertime-candy-wholesale-candy-canada_medium.jpg?v=1562964005" alt="Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>Most of your customers probably wait for Summer all year long so they can get outdoors and enjoy some of their favourite activities. A relaxing day poolside, a leisurely evening stroll, or maybe a cottage getaway. </div>
<div>What else could go better with fun Summertime activities? Candy of course! </div>
<div>The sun is shining, there is not a snowflake to be found and your customers have waited long enough for those hot summer rays.</div>
<div>Be sure your candy store is Summer ready! Fill your candy aisles with the sweet taste of Summer!</div>
<div></div>
<div>Here are some of our Best Selling Summertime Candy...</div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/lollipops" target="_blank" title="Everyone's a Sucker for Lollipops" rel="noopener noreferrer">Everyone's a Sucker for Lollipops</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/lollipops-suckers-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563061967" alt="Lollipops and Suckers-Best Selling Summer Candy"></p>
<div>Lollipops are great fun for an adventurous road trip. They'll keep everyone busy and sweetly entertain those excitable kids! They also double as a sweet microphone for all those must sing along with songs! With so many colours, sizes and shapes to choose from there are sure to be favourite for everyone.</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/candy-queen_medium.jpg?v=1563063194" alt="Candy Queen"></div>
<div>Our sweet selection includes the goodness of some old fashioned lollipops like <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/tootsie-pops-assorted?_pos=1&amp;_sid=e79b6d516&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Tootsie Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Tootsie Pop</strong></a> and <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/sugar-daddy?_pos=1&amp;_sid=137e06127&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Sugar Daddy Caramel Suckers" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Sugar Daddy Caramel Suckers</strong></a>. We also have some retro lollipops like the famous <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/astro-pop-original?_pos=1&amp;_sid=d5ac869d7&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Astro Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Astro Pop</strong></a>, and <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/charms-blow-pop" target="_blank" title="Charms Blow Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Charms Blow Pop</strong></a>.</div>
<div>For an extra amazing and eye-catching Lollipop, check out our <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/alberts-swirl-pops?_pos=1&amp;_sid=52b5889be&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Alberts Swirl Pops" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Alberts Swirl Pops</strong></a>. With their colourful, whimsical swirls, and delicious flavours, your candy store with be ten times sweeter, brighter and most importantly, Summertime ready!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bubble-gum" target="_blank" title="Blow Big Bubbles with Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer">Blow Big Bubbles with Bubble Gum</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/bubble-gum-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563062189" alt="Bubble Gum-Best Selling Summertime Candy"></p>
<div>This season is perfect for enticing your customers with Bubble Gum. It's a sweet treat for those long dog days of summer! Make them feel like a kid again with a pink, mouthwatering, juicy wad of bubblegum! Bubble gum is a staple for every candy aisle.</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/dubble-bubble-bubble-gum-retro-candy-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563066481" alt="Dubble Bubble Original Bubble Gum at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>Entice them with some old fashioned bubble gum like <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/dubble-bubble-gum-original-380-piece-tub?_pos=3&amp;_sid=af53590e9&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Dubble Bubble" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Dubble Bubble</strong></a>. Great for amusing talkative children during those long drives to the beach! Dubble Bubble also makes the perfect choice of gum for a fun Bubble Blowing competition! </div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/dubble-bubble-bubblegum-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy_medium.jpg?v=1563066207" alt="Dubble Bubble Bubblegum-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>Summer also means baseball! Impromptu games with friends, or watching it from the stands. We have the most fitting bubble gum for that! <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/big-league-chew" target="_blank" title="Big Leauge Chew Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Big Leauge Chew Bubble Gum</strong></a>. Choose from our delicious selection of flavours. whichever you choose, it's always a win-win situation with Big League Chew!</div>
<div>For a taste of nostalgia try some of our retro bubble gum. Our <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/gold-mine-bubble-gum?_pos=1&amp;_sid=f62d011be&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Gold Mine Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Gold Mine Bubble Gum</strong></a> is sure to be a hit with young and old alike. Gold nuggets of pure, juicy yumminess, and guess what? It still comes in that little burlap pouch. Great for collecting those tiny shells in the shore!</div>
<div>Or how about some sour bubble gum?</div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cry-baby-bubble-gum-sour-candy-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563067710" alt="Cry Baby Bubble Gum-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></div>
<div>If your brave and want a rush of sour satisfaction, we recommend the <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/cry-baby-bubble-gum-6-piece-tube?_pos=1&amp;_sid=ee268f496&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Cry Baby Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Cry Baby Bubble Gum</strong></a>. You'll just cringe at all the tangy sour delight!</div>
<div>  <strong>Fresh bubble gum will make your store a number one Summertime stop! </strong>
</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/salt-water-taffy" target="_blank" title="Salt Water Taffy is Sweet" rel="noopener noreferrer">Salt Water Taffy is Sweet</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/salt-water-taffy-old-fashioned-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1562898669" alt="Salt Water Taffy-Old Fashioned Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>If this candy does not induce the joys of Summer, what other candy could?  Stretchy, chewy and so very flavourful. Coming in a large variety of delicious flavours and also a multitude of colours.</div>
<div>Despite its name, there is really no salt water in Salt Water Taffy. This old fashioned candy came out in Atlantic City, New Jersey in the early 1880s, and remains an extremely popular candy choice to this day! </div>
<div>You don't need to be in Jersey to enjoy it' either!  Salt Water Taffy is a wonderful accompaniment to bring along to the cottage or beach. It would also make a great sweet treat to enjoy at the end of a fun family picnic, barbeque or a summer birthday party!</div>
<div>This melt in your mouth old fashioned candy will have your customers coming back time and time again! Be their summer candy destination with our fresh, and luscious Salt Water Taffy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/pop-rocks" target="_blank" title="Pop Rocks Candy are Popping Fun" rel="noopener noreferrer">Pop Rocks Candy are Popping Fun</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/pop-rocks-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563062479" alt="Pop Rocks-Best Selling Summertime Candy"></p>
<div>Have a blast this Summer with the explosive taste of our Pop Rocks Candy! Your candy section will definitely rock, and your customers will quiver with sweet anticipation!  </div>
<div>This retro candy goes hand in hand with Summer! A fun treat to eat while watching fireworks and a great afternoon pick me up after a long and tiring swim!</div>
<div>Despite the rumour, your stomach will not explode! Just the tastebuds in your mouth! Pop Rocks candy has been around since 1975, and are still a totally amazing, must have candy!</div>
<div>Choose from our wide selection of Pop Rocks, or mix a few mouthfuls from different packs! Whichever way you enjoy them the flavour will cause a delicious burst of intense deliciousness!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/wonka-candy" target="_blank" title="The Sweet Genius of Wonka Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">The Sweet Genius of Wonka Candy</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/willy-wonka-candies-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563062796" alt="Willy Wonka Candy-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>You'll be sure to keep those candy lovers coming back for more with the delicious fun of Wonka Candy! This retro candy is always a top choice for candy connoisseurs. It's innovative, colourful and as Willy Wonka would say "scrumpdillyicious"! </div>
<div>Our collection of Wonka Candy includes all the must-have classics like <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/nerds-candy" target="_blank" title="Nerds Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Nerds Candy</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-everlasting-gobstopper?_pos=1&amp;_sid=1e54aa7bb&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Everlasting Gobstoppers" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Everlasting Gobstoppers</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-fundip?_pos=1&amp;_sid=6164ddabb&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Fun Dip" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Fun Dip</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-bottle-caps-rolls?_pos=1&amp;_sid=cb0b74ae0&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Bottle Caps" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Bottle Caps</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-sweetarts-rolls?_pos=2&amp;_sid=5ca2531f8&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Sweetarts" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Sweetarts</strong></a>, <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-laffy-taffy-assorted-tub?_pos=1&amp;_sid=e0cbdc83a&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Laffy Taffy" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Laffy Taffy</strong></a> and <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-runts?_pos=2&amp;_sid=118a38b89&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Runts Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Runts Candy</strong></a>. Include them all in your candy section for optimum and sweet results!</div>
<div>Be the Candy Store that's on the top of their list with our fabulous Wonka Candy!</div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/novelty-candy" target="_blank" title="Kidsmania Puts the Fun in the Munch" rel="noopener noreferrer">Kidsmania Puts the Fun in the Munch</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kidsmania-novelty_candy-toys-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy-canada.jpg?v=1563067072" alt="Kidsmania Novelty Candy-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>Have a candy section that's not only known for delicious candy but fun! With our collection of Kidsmania Novelty Candy. You'll be able to entertain your customers and fill their sweet tooths also!</div>
<div>Kidsmania Candy is not only a sweet treat but comes in the form of a toy! Filled with amusing fun for endless hours of making great memories with family and friends. Makes a fantastic Summertime candy. Light up the dark while your camping with the Kidsmania Blink Pops, or turn that rainy day at the cottage into a Kidsmania car race. The possibilities are endless and the candy delicious!</div>
<div>Kidsmania is an interactive candy. Very suitable for the Summer season. It's also a good way to keep the kids busy before they start complaining that they're bored on their summer holidays. Amuse them with our wide selection of Kidsmania Candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/rock-candy-sticks" target="_blank" title="Old Fashioned Rock Candy Sticks" rel="noopener noreferrer">Old Fashioned Rock Candy Sticks</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/rock-candy-sticks-retro-candy.jpg?v=1562888440" alt="Rock Candy Sticks Retro Candies"></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"> </p>
<div>Not only is this such a pretty candy to look at, but our Rock Candy tastes great! A very popular Old fashioned Candy that nowadays can be hard to come by. </div>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Delight your customers as they remember the good old days!</strong></div>
<div>Rock Candy would also be a fantastic extra on a dessert table at a wedding, or shower or add to a candy bar.</div>
<div>Coming in a wide variety of colours and flavours you're sure to find your favourite!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/life-savers-candy" target="_blank" title="Life Savers Candy are a Hole Lot of Fun" rel="noopener noreferrer">Life Savers Candy are a Hole Lot of Fun</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/life-savers-retro-candy-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy_medium.jpg?v=1563067925" alt="Life Savers Retro Candy-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>This old fashioned candy is a classic! Make your store a "hole" Lot of fun for your customers with Life Savers Candy. This well-loved candy is also convenient as it comes in rolls that can easily fit in a pocket. Great for those gruelling Summer activities when you might need a sweet pick me up! </div>
<div>Just like Summer, Life Saver Candies are succulent and sweet! Help your customers to beat the heat with this famously delicious old fashioned candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/bazooka-candy-brands" target="_blank" title="Bazooka Candy Brands" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bazooka Candy Brands</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/bazooka-candy-brands-baby-bottle-pops-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.jpg?v=1562887975" alt="Bazooka Candy Brands-Retro Candy Canada"></p>
<div>Bring the party to your candy section with Bazooka Candy Brands! They are delicious, bright and fun! A great summertime candy brand that is also very amusing!</div>
<div>Ring Pop will make a sweet fashion statement at the beach, and the Push Pop is ideal for travelling, especially the Triple Power Push Pop! Don't forget the Garbage Candy, that's always entertaining!</div>
<div>The Bazooka Candy Brand line of candy is perfect for summer, always fresh, tasty and so very amusing! </div>
<div></div>
<h3><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/licorice-candy" target="_blank" title="Sweet and Salty Licorice Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sweet and Salty Licorice Candy</a></h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn2.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/licorice-candy-best-selling-summertime-candy-i-wholesale-candy_medium.jpg?v=1563068249" alt="Licorice Candy-Best Selling Summertime Candy at Wholesale Prices"></p>
<div>Licorice Candy is a great addition to every candy aisle! It's a classic old fashioned candy that is loved by all ages!</div>
<div>Licorice is a great choice for summer. It doesn't melt in the sun and is a convenient on the go snack!</div>
<div>For the sophisticated black licorice lover, check out our old fashioned <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/mccormicks-licorice-babies-candy?_pos=1&amp;_sid=af2fa676e&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Licorice Babies" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Licorice Babies</strong></a>! Or <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/good-plenty-licorice-candy-theater-box?_pos=1&amp;_sid=864adb053&amp;_ss=r" target="_blank" title="Good and Plenty" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Good and Plenty</strong></a>, these will bring back some sweet summertime memories!</div>
<div>Our Licorice Laces are delicious and great fun. Tie them in a knot or tie them in a bow but whatever you do, you simply must have them in your candy section!</div>
<div>Licorice Candy is a sweet, old fashioned Summertime favourite!</div>
<div></div>
<div>Help your customers to beat the heat with our Best Selling Summertime Candy!</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Fresh Candy Shipped Fast at Wholesale Prices!</h3>
<div style="text-align: center;"><strong>Give them some sweet fun in the sun with the freshest selection of the best selling summertime candy at wholesale prices! Your customers deserve it!</strong></div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-novelty-candies</id>
    <published>2018-12-24T01:34:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-24T01:40:08-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-novelty-candies"/>
    <title>Top 10 Selling Novelty Candies</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>For the ultimate experience in candy and fun, Novelty Candy makes everything sweeter! The combination of candy and a toy is not only yummy but also highly amusing! Entertain the kids, your friends, and yourself with some delicious and  Novelty Candy. Here is a list of our Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-selling-novelty-candies">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;"><span>Play with your candy and eat it too!</span></h2>
<p><span>For the ultimate experience in candy and fun, Novelty Candy makes everything sweeter! The combination of candy and a toy is not only yummy but also highly amusing! Entertain the kids, your friends, and yourself with some delicious and  Novelty Candy.</span></p>
<div>Your customers will love delving into the playful and yumminess of all that colourful and exciting Candy! Make your store their source for all of their Novelty Candy needs. This tasty and lively candy is perfect for some funny gag gifts, Birthday Party Favours or as an addition to Loot Bags. </div>
<div>  Here is our list of the Top Ten Selling Novelty Candies...</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/triple-power-push-pop-candy-16-ct" target="_blank" title="Triple Power Push Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer">Triple Power Push Pop</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/topps-triple-power-push-pop-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545627825" alt="Top 10 Novelty Candy-Topps Triple Power Push Pop Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>Triple your Lollipop game with the Triple Power Push Pop! A mouthwatering, delicious lollipop that comes with three, yes, three juicy flavours! Eat it all at once, or save some for later, you're in charge with a Push Pop! A fun and delicious novelty lollipop that everybody will love! Flavours include Strawberry, Watermelon, and Blue Rasberry, Twisted Rainbow Sherbet,  Berry Blast, Strawberry Watermelon. Give your customers "Triple" the pleasure with the Triple Power Push Pops! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-sour-flush" target="_blank" title="Sour Flush Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sour Flush Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-sour-flush-toilet-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545628424" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Sour Flush Toilet Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>This is one toilet you won't mind being so close to! This special Sour Flush toilet comes filled with Sour Candy powder inside. Dip the miniature lollipop plunger to gather all that tart sour powder inside the toilet, then eat it off the plunger lollipop. A fun and tasty novelty candy that would also work as a very funny gag gift. Kids love the shock value of the Sour Flush Toilet, they'll be in disbelief of a toilet that includes candy! A fun and tasty candy that would make any party favour extra exciting and humorous. You won't be bothered by eating from this Sour Flush Toilet bowl!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/novelty-candy/products/kidsmania-quick-blast" target="_blank" title="Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray" rel="noopener noreferrer">Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-quick-blast-sour-spray-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545628753" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray Wholesale Candies"></p>
<div>Put out your sour candy craving with the Quick Blast  Sour Candy Spray. Just shoot this fire extinguisher right inside your mouth for a delicious "Quick Blast" of yummy Sour Candy! Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray comes in three tart and sour flavours, Green Apple Burst, Blue Raspberry Blast, Cherry Splash. Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray would be great for a firefighter themed birthday party, also a great party favour to include in a loot bag. Extinguish your customer's sour cravings easily with the Quick Blast Sour Candy Spray!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-candy-jackpot" target="_blank" title="Candy Jackpot " rel="noopener noreferrer">Candy Jackpot </a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-candy-jackpot-slot-machine-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545629007" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Candy Jackpot Slot Machine Wholesale Candy"></p>
<p> </p>
<div>Hit the Jackpot and try your luck with the Bubble Gum filled Candy Jackpot! I bet you'll win, just pull the Jackpot lever down and this sweet Candy Jackpot will dispense to you colourful and flavourful Dubble Bubble Gumballs! It's a win-win situation with this fun and exciting Candy Toy!  The Candy Jackpot would be great to have at a party or to add into a candy loot bag. Everybody gets lucky with the sweet filled Dubble Bubble Candy Jackpot! A Novelty Candy that will make all your candy-loving customers feel "lucky"!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-laser-pop" target="_blank" title="Laser Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer">Laser Pop</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/laser_pop.jpg?v=1545629263" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Laser Pop Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>Find your way in a dark room with the illumination of the Kidsmania Laser Pop! This Lollipop is not only a delicious candy treat but will sweetly light up your life! Comes in a variety of cool laser shapes that you can project onto dark surfaces. The shapes include hearts, stars, a UFO, or a whale. A great give away in a loot bag, a fun candy toy for birthday party sleepovers! The Lollipop flavours include Blue Raspberry, Strawberry Burst and Cherry Blast. Make your candy aisle bright with Laser Pops!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#6. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-happy-van" target="_blank" title="Happy Van" rel="noopener noreferrer">Happy Van</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-happy-van-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545629519" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Happy Van Novelty Candy Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>Get in touch with your inner hippie with this groovy looking Happy Van. Filled with an assortment of delicious fruity tasting candy. A fun toy to play with after you eat all the candy. The Happy Van would be great for a 60's or 70's themed party. Ideal for a party favour or a loot bag. The Happy Van will amuse every kid at heart plus give you candy! What could be better? Stock your candy aisle with the sweet grooviness of peace, love and candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/novelty-candy" target="_blank" title="Wack Monkey" rel="noopener noreferrer">Wack Monkey</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-wacky-monkey-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545629771" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Wacky Monkey Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>The next best thing to a pet monkey! This monkey is filled to the brim with candy and will clap it's cymbals together for you. A must have as an entertaining party favour, a fabulous addition to a loot bag. The Wacky Monkey is not only super cute but fun and amusing for all ages. This novelty candy is a must-have in your candy section and is deliciously approved for "monkeying" around with!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#8. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/baby-bottle-pop-candy-18-ct" target="_blank" title="Baby Bottle Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer">Baby Bottle Pop</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-topps-baby-bottle-pop-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545630405" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Topps Baby Bottle Pop Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>Baby your cute candy cravings with the tasty Baby Bottle Pop. A baby Bottle that is filled with delicious, powdery candy. simply remove the top of the bottle and start dipping into all that fantastic powdery sweetness! Comes in four flavours, Watermelon, Strawberry, Cotton Candy and Blue Raspberry. The Baby Bottle Pop would be the most adorable novelty candy at a gender reveal party or a baby shower. A fun and amusing candy toy to add to a loot bag. A sweet and darling candy that your enticing candy aisle needs!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/novelty-candy/products/kidsmania-soda-can" target="_blank" title="Soda Can Fizzy Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Soda Can Fizzy Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-soda-can-fizzy-wholesale-candy.png?v=1545630716" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Soda Can Fizzy Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>A miniature Soda can that is filled with sweet, fizzy candy! A cute take on soda flavoured candy. Comes in some of your most favourite and popular soda flavours, Grape Splash, Lemon-Lime Sprint, Orange Crash and Loca Cola.</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-soda-can-fizzy-wholesale-candy-mississauga.png?v=1545630896" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Soda Can Fizzy Wholesale Candy Toronto"></div>
<div>The Soda Can Novelty Candy would be a sweet decorative tabletop element for a birthday party, or to hold up place cards on a table. A wonderful treat to add to a loot bag or to give away as a party favour. Let your customers feel like a kid again with these amusing and fun Soda Can Candies!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-sweet-soaker" target="_blank" title="Sweet Soaker" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sweet Soaker</a>
</h3>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-sweet-soaker-wholesale-candy-mississauga.png?v=1545631354" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Sweet Soaker Candy Filled Squirt Guns 12-Piece Box Wholesale Candy"></p>
<div>Have a water war with your friends after a sweet sugar rush! The Sweet Soaker is a mini squirt gun that is filled with little flavourful jawbreaker candies. Once you're done indulging in the candy, fill it up with water and start soaking! You won't be sad when the candy's all gone, there's more fun to come!</div>
<div><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/top-10-selling-novelty-candy-kidsmania-sweet-soaker-candy-filled-squirt-guns-12-piece-box-wholesale-candy-mississauga.png?v=1545631456" alt="Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Kidsmania Top 10 Selling Novelty Candy-Sweet Soaker Candy Filled Squirt Guns Wholesale Candy"></div>
<div>A magnificent Novelty Candy for an outdoor birthday party, picnic or a barbeque. Your family and friends won't know what they're in for with the Sweet Soaker! A must have Novelty Candy that your customers will be thrilled to find in your store.</div>
<h3>Add sweet times to any party with Novelty Candy!</h3>
<div></div>
<div>Eat the Candy, then play! Mom would even approve, it's pure sweet fun! Novelty Candy is sure to make a splash at any occasion or birthday party and is a welcome addition to a candy loot bag. Make them smile and laugh, plus feed them some candy! Great exciting fun for kids of all ages.</div>
<h3>Check out all the<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/novelty-candy" target="_blank" title=" Novelty Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Novelty Candy</a> at Wholesale Prices!</h3>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-candies-to-take-to-the-movies</id>
    <published>2018-08-16T13:40:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-12-24T01:08:56-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-candies-to-take-to-the-movies"/>
    <title>Top 10 Candies to take to the Movies</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div>An over-sized Theater Box, filled with your favourite candy always makes any "blockbuster" that much more enjoyable, or tolerable! The candy is sometimes the most deserving of the leading role. Candy is always a memorable part of any movie! </div>
<div>Here is our list of the Top 10 candies to take to the movie.</div><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-candies-to-take-to-the-movies">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;">Take a Theater Pack to Your Favourite Candy</h2>
<div>The one thing that can make any movie even sweeter no matter the plot, is the addition of candy! Whether you're at home binge-watching the latest critically acclaimed series or seated at the movie theater behind someone's oversized head. An over-sized Theater Box, filled with your favourite candy always makes any "blockbuster" that much more enjoyable, or tolerable! The candy is sometimes the most deserving of the leading role. Candy is always a memorable part of any movie! </div>
<div></div>
<div>Here is our list of the Top 10 candies to take to the movies:</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/junior-mints-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Junior Mints Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Junior Mints Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/junior-mints-chocolate-mint-candy-theater-pack-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534436323" alt="Junior Mints Candy Theater Packs"></p>
<div>A refreshing and sweet treat that is the #1 selling candy at the movies. An old fashioned candy confection that always stirs up our taste buds with that intense, dark chocolate and peppermint taste. A retro candy since 1949 that was actually named after a Broadway musical. It's only fitting then, that Junior Mints are the perfect accompaniment (or date) to any movie. A refreshing and delectable peppermint that is covered with rich dark chocolate. If you plan on sharing, you might need two boxes! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/sugar-babies-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Sugar Babies Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sugar Babies Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/sugar-babies-candy-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534439188" alt="Sugar Babies Candy Theater Box"></p>
<p> </p>
<div>This candy-coated caramel candy goes perfectly after some hot buttery popcorn! Sugar Babies are the sweet child of the "Sugar Daddy"  caramel lollipop. But this retro candy is easier and more convenient to eat, especially in public. The caramel is a milk caramel that is slow cooked and covered in a very thin caramel candy shell. It's like a double serving of caramel with two different textures. Sugar Babies Candy are smooth and delightful tasting, so chewy and very satisfying. A candy lovers indulgence, a bite-size taste of caramel candy bliss!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/reeses-pieces-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Reese's Pieces Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Reese's Pieces Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/reeses-pieces-peanut-butter-candy-theater-packs-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534436884" alt="Reese's Pieces Candy Theater Packs"></p>
<div>A peanut buttery middle that is surrounded in a crunchy delicious candy shell. Reese's Pieces Candy is a staple for every movie!  After all, they are E.T's most favourite candy. Apparently, some folks say, adding Reese's Pieces Candy to a bag of popcorn makes for an amazing combination. With or without a popcorn partner, Reese's Pieces are a retro candy that can stand alone any day. There is no other candy that compares to that smooth peanut butter middle and sweet candy crunch. A perfect pairing!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/hot-tamales-fierce-cinnamon-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Hot Tamales Fierce Cinnamon Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Hot Tamales Fierce Cinnamon Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hot-tamales-fierce-cinnamon-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534437218" alt="Hot Tamales Fierce Cinnamon Candy Theater Box"></p>
<div>Spice up any movie date with some Hot Tamales Candy! A sweet and spicy candy with the intense taste of cinnamon. Hot Tamales Fierce Cinnamon Candy come with some heat and you may just find yourself shedding a tear. An especially good candy to eat during a tear-jerker so you can blame those tears on the hot candy! Hot Tamales Fierce Cinnamon Candy are an old fashioned candy from the 1950's and are still a popular candy today. Add some spice and intoxicate your taste buds with the fierce cinnamon flavour of Hot Tamales! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/raisinets-milk-chocolate-covered-raisins-theater-box" target="_blank" title="RAISINETS MILK CHOCOLATE COVERED RAISINS THEATER BOX" rel="noopener noreferrer">Rasinets Milk Chocolate Covered Raisins Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/rasinets-milk-chocolate-covered-raisins-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534437599" alt="Rasinets Milk Chocolate Covered Raisins Theater Box"></p>
<div>Plump and juicy California Raisins that are covered in Nestle's rich milk chocolate makes everything that much sweeter! Raisinets Milk Chocolate Covered Raisins have been around since 1927, an old fashioned candy that makes for a classic movie time snack. This iconic candy has been poured out of the box by the handfuls, or directly from the box into the anticipating mouths of those craving this classic candy combination. Everything changes, but Raisnets Candy remain a number one movie time snack across theaters everywhere! Raisnets Milk Chocolate Covered Raisins seem to disappear fast, you might need two theater boxes of this candy!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/everlasting-gobstopper-jawbreakers-theater-box" target="_blank" title=" Everlasting Gobstopper Jawbreakers Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Everlasting Gobstopper Jawbreakers Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/everlasting-gobstopper-jawbreakers-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534437881" alt="Wonka Everlasting Gobstopper Jawbreakers Theater Box"></p>
<div>Layer upon delicious layer, this retro candy will be "everlasting" through any movie. The Everlasting Gobstopper Jawbreakers Theater Box is the perfect companion for any movie. Intense flavour that is long lasting, a sweet and delightful palate cleanser after all that salty popcorn. From the sweet genius himself, Willy Wonka (and also a box office star). Everlasting Gobstoppers are every bit of fun as they are "scrumpdillyicious". A retro candy with the magical, never-ending sweetness of Wonka!  Everlasting Gobstoppers Jawbreakers come in five fantastic, fruity flavours including:  Watermelon, Cherry, Orange, Lemon, and Grape.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/good-plenty-licorice-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Good And Plenty Licorice Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Good And Plenty Licorice Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/good-and-plenty-licorice-candy-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534438095" alt="Good And Plenty Licorice Candy Theater Box"></p>
<div>Since 1893, Good And Plenty Licorice Candy have graced the open hands and hungry mouths of many candy lovers everywhere! A top choice when it comes to that authentic black licorice flavour. With a black licorice center that is coated with pink and white candied shells, you get a perfect light crunch in every morsel of Good And Plenty. A great sidekick for any movie, ideal for sharing, but be sure to get "plenty". They mysteriously seem to vanish quite fast, especially in a dark theatre. Good And Plenty are that good!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/milk-duds-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Milk Duds Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Milk Duds Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/milk-duds-chocolate-caramel-candy-theater-packs-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534436648" alt="Milk Duds Candy Theater Box"></p>
<div>Even if the movie turns out to be a "dud", your candy doesn't have to be! Milk Duds Candy Theater Box makes for an irresistible movie time snack, actually any time snack! If you happen to be watching a scary movie be careful not to get so scared that the Milk Duds go flying out of the box! You can't afford to miss any delectable morsels of this retro candy! A chewy and creamy delicious caramel middle that is covered in milk chocolate. Milk Duds Candy gives you caramel and chocolate, all in one candy. It's a double serving of pure and exquisite mouthwatering enjoyment!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/mike-and-ike-original-fruits-candy-theater-box" target="_blank" title="Mike And Ike Original Fruits Candy Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mike And Ike Original Fruits Candy Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/mike-and-ike-original-fruits-candy-theater-box-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534438453" alt="MIKE AND IKE ORIGINAL FRUITS CANDY THEATER BOX"></p>
<div>A refreshing and fruity confection, Mike And Ike Original Fruits Candy make for a chewy and yummy movie time candy! A favourite candy of many since it's release in 1940. This old fashioned candy is made with real fruit juice, giving it an even more intense and fruity taste! Mike And Ike Original Fruits Candy in a Theater Box come in five extreme, super fruity flavours including Cherry, Lemon, Orange, Lime, and Strawberry. Try them all! The <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/theater-boxes" target="_blank" title="Mike And Ike Candy Collection" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Mike And Ike Candy Collection</strong></a> comes in a variety of fun flavours, sure to excite every candy lover around, even during the most boring movie! </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/nestle-buncha-crunch-theater-box" target="_blank" title=" Nestle Buncha Crunch Theater Box" rel="noopener noreferrer"> Nestle Buncha Crunch Theater Box</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/nestle-buncha-crunch-theater-boxes-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534438804" alt="NESTLE BUNCHA CRUNCH THEATER BOX"></p>
<div>A crunchy and delicious chocolatey candy treat that makes a great dessert after all that salty popcorn! Nestle Buncha Crunch is an ideal candy for an enticing movie. The added crunch seems to make any drama that much more intense! Crispy rice bits that are generously smothered in rich milk chocolate, Buncha Crunch has loads of delightful texture and taste. This crunch is deliciously addictive, you'll definitely have the urge to munch on tons of this candy! Be prepared if you plan on sharing, and have extra. The roller coaster of emotions that a good chick flick can induce will make you extra hungry! Nestle Buncha Crunch Theater Box makes a fantastic indulgence.</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Indulge in a Box of Movie Time Candy</h3>
<div></div>
<div>Candy in a Theater Box is a great way to get that extra amount of candy you love to eat!  Whether you're watching a movie or not, it's always a great time for some candy! Make some fun new memories with our Candy Theater Boxes. They're award-winning and most definitely, Oscar-worthy!</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Every Candy Aisle needs a Theater Box Section</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Every Candy Aisle needs a Theater Box Section" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/every-candy-aisle-needs-a-theater-box-candy-section-i-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1534441184" style="float: none;"></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Check out our <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/theater-boxes" target="_blank" title="Theater Box Candy collection" rel="noopener noreferrer">Theater Box Candy collection</a> today!</h3>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies</id>
    <published>2018-08-13T21:05:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-08-13T21:05:20-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies"/>
    <title>Your Store Needs The Best Top 10 Sour Candies</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>All the sour candy that your customers need! Let them fall to their knees with the tangiest, sourest, cringe-inducing sour candy there is! Every candy aisle needs a large and exciting selection of sour candy, and every sour candy lover needs a well-stocked store that fills all of their sour cravings!</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;">Your Sweet Customers Want Sour Candy</h2>
<div>All the sour candy that your customers need! Let them fall to their knees with the tangiest, sourest, cringe-inducing sour candy there is! Every candy aisle needs a large and exciting selection of sour candy, and every sour candy lover needs a well-stocked store that fills all of their sour cravings!</div>
<div>Get ready to pucker up! We've made you a list of our top 10 Sour Candies.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/jumbo-sour-suckers" target="_blank" title="Koala Jumbo Sour Suckers" rel="noopener noreferrer">Koala Jumbo Sour Suckers</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/koala-jumbo-sour-soothers-gummy-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534202183" alt="Koala Jumbo Sour Suckers Candy"></p>
<div>These sour candies often go by some different names, such as Sour Keys, Sour Soothers or Sour Suckers. Whatever you may call them, they are a number one selling sour candy. Jumbo Sour Suckers are one of the most popular sour gummy candies sold. In the tangy world of sour candies, these are essential to have stocked in your candy section. Sour, gummy candy with a key like shape, that are covered in granules of sweet sugar just to help with the sour sting. Every candy lover seeks the deliciousness of Koala Jumbo Sour Suckers! </div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#2.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/allan-big-foot-sour-blue-raspberry-candy" target="_blank" title="Allan Big Foot Sour Blue Raspberry" rel="noopener noreferrer">Allan Big Foot Sour Blue Raspberry</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/allan-big-foot-sour-blue-raspberry-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534202679" alt="Allan Big Foot Sour Blue Raspberry Candy"></p>
<div>Prepare to have your sour candy wants to be squashed with the Allan Big Foot Sour Blue Raspberry Candy. A Canadian candy, that is the not so distant cousin to the Allan Big Foot Original but with a sour twist. Yes, feet can really smell good, and the Allan Big Foot Sour Blue Raspberry candies really do! With a raspberry flavour and a balance of zingy sour, they are also made with real fruit juice! Be sure to check out the whole line of our <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/allan-candy" target="_blank" title="Allan Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>Allan Candy</strong></a>.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/albanese-sour-assorted-fruit-gummi-bears" target="_blank" title="Albanese Sour Fruit Gummi Bears" rel="noopener noreferrer">Albanese Sour Fruit Gummi Bears</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/albanese-sour-gummy-bears-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534202919" alt="Albanese Fruiti Sour Gummy Bears Candy"></p>
<div>Sure, these bears look cute but watch out. They bite back with their sourness! Albanese Sour Fruit Gummi Bears are a soft and chewy, fruity flavoured sour candy. Albanese Sour fruit Gummi Bears come in six, sour and tangy flavours including Cherry, Apple, Pineapple, Orange, Lemon and Watermelon. Mouthwatering, fruity and perfectly chewy, a great sour candy to share or to use in a colourful candy buffet. Your customers will come to expect these cute Gummy Bears in your sour candy section. Give your sweet customers some very sour bears!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/toxic-waste-sour-candy-drums" target="_blank" title="Toxic Waste Sour Candy Drums" rel="noopener noreferrer">Toxic Waste Sour Candy Drums</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/toxic-waste-hazardously-sour-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534203807" alt="#4. Toxic Waste Sour Candy Drums "></p>
<div>When they say that "Toxic Waste" is hazardous, we take them quite seriously. You will too after eating this seriously sour candy! Toxic Waste Sour Candy Drums are individually wrapped sour candies that are outrageously sour, and will make you squirm! Not for the faint of heart, but for every sour candy section around! The "toxic" sourness does subside after about 20-30 seconds and you're left with a nice and well rounded sweet candy. Or so you think! Beware inside the very center there are more sour surprise tastes to be had! Toxic Waste Sour Candy comes in 5 fantastically sour flavours including Apple, Lemon, Watermelon, Blue Raspberry and Black Cherry. "We Dare You", as this sour candy states, to entice all your customers will the shrilling tartness and sour taste of Toxic Waste Sour Candy.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/power-poppers-sour-foam-candy" target="_blank" title="Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/sour-poppers-sour-foam-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534204121" alt="#5.Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy"></p>
<div>A fun and entertaining sour candy! A yummy and novelty candy all in one! The Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy comes in a foamy consistency that you can spray directly into your mouth. A unique and fun way to get your sour candy fix! The Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy is highly entertaining, great for a gag gift, or even a surprise spray in the face at a birthday party. Get your camera's ready for some funny faces! The Sour Poppers Sour Foam Candy comes in three fun and foamy flavours including Green Apple, Strawberry and Blue Raspberry. Give your store some excitement, and your customers some foamy and sour candy fun!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-sweetarts-chewy-sours-rolls" target="_blank" title="Sweetarts Chewy Sours" rel="noopener noreferrer">Sweetarts Chewy Sours</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/sweetarts-chewy-sours-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534204330" alt="Sweetarts Chewy Sours Candy"></p>
<div>We can thank Willy Wonka for these sour candy treats! Sweetarts Chewy Sours are deliciously yummy, chewy and have a balance of delicate tanginess. You won't cry tears of sour candy joy as these are more of a tolerable taste. Sweetarts Chewy Sours was once known as "Shockers" but have since had a name change. A retro candy that's a great choice for a first time sour candy newbie. Sweetarts Chewy Sours come in Red, Green, Purple, Blue and Orange. A sour candy from Willy Wonka that will add some sour flair to any candy aisle!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/kidsmania-sour-soda-pop" target="_blank" title="Kidsmania Sour Soda Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer">Kidsmania Sour Soda Pop</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/kidsmania-sour-soda-pop-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534207565" alt="Kidsmania Sour Soda Pop Candy"></p>
<div>This sour candy is not only yummy to eat, but also super fun to play with! Kidsmania Sour Soda Pop are tiny pop bottles that are filled with tangy, sour powder. You'll enjoy opening these miniature bottles and pouring the sour candy powder in your mouth. A fun and entertaining sour candy for everyone! Also a great addition to any gift. Kidsmania Sour Soda Pop comes in Cherry, Cola, Lemon and Green Apple. An amusing sour candy for every candy section!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/warheads-smashups-extreme-sour-hard-candy" target="_blank" title="Warheads Smash Up Extreme Sour Hard Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Warheads Smash Up Extreme Sour Hard Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/warheads-smash-up-extreme-sour-hard-candy-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534208068" alt="Warheads Smash Up Extreme Sour Hard Candy"></p>
<div>Warheads Candy already take sour to a whole new level. But the Warheads Smash Up Extreme Sour Hard Candy are just that, extremely sour! This hard sour candy has combined two intensely sour flavours all into one candy! Now you can double your sour candy pleasure! The tangy and mouthwatering combinations include Strawberry/Grape, Orange/Pineapple, Mango/Melon, Lemon/Berry, and Cherry/Lime. The Warheads Smash Up Extreme Sour Hard Candy is just waiting for your lips to pucker and your body to quiver with their exciting and extreme sour taste! Give them a sour extreme, a must have sour candy in your candy aisle.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/cry-baby-bubble-gum-6-piece-tube" target="_blank" title="Cry Baby Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer">Cry Baby Bubble Gum</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/cry-baby-bubble-gum-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534208330" alt="Cry Baby Bubble Gum"></p>
<div>This sour bubble gum really could make somebody cry, but only tears of sour candy joy! A sour, retro bubble gum that has smacked the keen, bubble blowing lips of many, for generations! The sourness of this bubble gum lasts for about 40 seconds until you begin to chew on a more tolerable, sweeter level of bubble gum. But, will you be brave enough to bite into this mouthwatering, sour bubble gum? Or will you turn into a cry baby? We hope not!  Don't make your customers cry, toughen up their taste buds with the Cry Baby Bubble Gum.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/jelly-belly-sours-jelly-beans" target="_blank" title="Jelly Belly Sours Jelly Beans" rel="noopener noreferrer">Jelly Belly Sours Jelly Beans</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/jelly-belly-sourpjelly-beans-your-store-needs-the-best-top-10-sour-candies-i-wholesale-candy-canada_large.png?v=1534208590" alt="Jelly Belly Sour Jelly Beans Bulk Candy"></p>
<div>These charming, old-fashioned jelly beans are sweet but also have a sour kick! Jelly Belly Sours Jelly Beans are a gourmet jelly bean that comes in superb flavours. With the perfect balance of sweet and sour, these sour jelly beans come in an assortment of five amazing flavours including Sour Cherry, Sour Apple, Sour Grape, Sour Lemon, and Sour Peach. These mouthwatering old fashioned jelly beans are not only deliciously fruity and sour, they come in an array of brilliant colours. A great choice to add a touch of sour zing to a candy buffet! Jelly Belly Sours Jelly Beans are a wonderful addition to any candy section.</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Add Excitement to your Candy Section</h3>
<div></div>
<div>Sour Candy is such an important candy to have stocked in your candy aisles. A popular and top-selling candy that will always keep those sour candy lovers coming back for more...and more! Those who love sour candy are always trying to top their latest sour candy experience. That's part of the thrill and adventure of all that pungent, lip puckering sour candy. Give them the sourest candy adventure you can and stock up!</div>
<h4 style="text-align: center;">
<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/sour-candy" target="_blank" title="Check out all the exciting Sour Candy here" rel="noopener noreferrer">Check out all the exciting Sour Candy here</a>!</h4>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-american-chocolate-bars-you-need-to-have</id>
    <published>2018-07-25T20:06:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-07-25T20:10:09-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-american-chocolate-bars-you-need-to-have"/>
    <title>Top 10 American Chocolate Bars You Need To Have</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>American Chocolate Bars will peak your customers interest with the promise of something new, different and delicious. American Chocolate Bars are a hard to find item. Be the store that has it all including a fresh and large selection of American Chocolate Bars.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/top-10-american-chocolate-bars-you-need-to-have">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;">Every Candy Section Needs American Chocolate Bars</h2>
<div>What would the world of candy be without chocolate bars? Now imagine the world without American Chocolate Bars. That's not sweet! Embarking on a not so typical chocolate bar is a fun adventure for any candy lover. Let your store be the sweet spot where they find their chocolate bliss!  <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/american-chocolate-bars" target="_blank" title="American Chocolate Bars" rel="noopener noreferrer"><strong>American Chocolate Bars</strong></a> will peak your customers interest with the promise of something new, different and delicious. American Chocolate Bars are a hard to find item. Be the store that has it all including a fresh and large selection of American Chocolate Bars.</div>
<div></div>
<div>Here are our top 10 American Chocolate Bars that have been consistent best sellers for generations:</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/100-grand-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="100 Grand Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">100 Grand Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/100-grand-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1532559824" alt="100 Grand American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>The 100 Grand Bar sounds like a rich and chocolatey experience. That's because it is! It has a rich and chewy caramel center, covered in crispy rice pieces that are enrobed in a delicious milk chocolate. This Chocolate Bar first came out in 1966 making it a classic retro candy treat. It was originally called $100,000 Bar which was spoken as "the hundred thousand dollar bar". This changed during the mid 1980's to the simpler 100 Grand. "That's Rich!" is the slogan for this Chocolate Bar and has not changed since it's release. The slogan is perfect for this rich American Chocolate Bar.</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#2. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/5th-avenue-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="5th Avenue Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">5th Avenue Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/5th-avenue-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy-canada.png?v=1532560007" alt="5th Avenue American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>Sounds like something only the elite can eat as they walk and shop along the ritzy 5th Avenue. This American Chocolate bar is an old fashioned candy bar that came out in 1936. It consists of a crunchy peanut butter middle that is covered in milk chocolate. It's crispy peanut butter middle is well loved for it's crunchiness and is the perfect partner for that smooth and rich milk chocolate. The original Chocolate Bar also had almonds alongside the crispy middle but not long after it's release the almonds were dropped from the bar. Who cares what street you're walking on if you've got a 5th Avenue American Chocolate Bar!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#3. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/almond-joy-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="Almond Joy Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Almond Joy Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/almond-joy-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532561305" alt="Almond Joy American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div><strong>Sometimes you feel like a nut...</strong></div>
<div>Yes, this Chocolate Bar really does bring "joy". It's that delicious! With almonds, coconut and chocolate you just can't go wrong. This bar will make you feel like your somewhere tropical, maybe exotic, sipping a cool drink beside the pool and watching the palm trees blow in the air. Okay, we know your not there but the point is that this American Chocolate Bar really does capture every flavor of the tropics. The flavor is very apparent and the tiny crunch of the almonds practically makes this bar. They are a great match for all that creamy and luscious coconut. The milk chocolate just beautifully ties this bar together. There is also a version available in dark chocolate. They are both equally fantastic. This is an amazing American Chocolate Bar that your customers will fall in love with.</div>
<div></div>
<div>
<h3>#4. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/mounds-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="Mounds Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Mounds Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/mounds-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532561517" alt="Mounds American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div><strong>...sometimes you don't!</strong></div>
<div>This is the cousin to the previously mentioned "Almond Joy" but with no almonds. The Mounds Bar is very straight forward kind of bar. This delicious chocolate bar is made with a fresh tasting shredded coconut middle that is covered with luscious dark chocolate. Perhaps it's simplicity is what makes this American Chocolate Bar so irresistible. When you don't feel like a nut, this is the exact Chocolate Bar to reach for.</div>
</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#5.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/baby-ruth-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Baby Ruth Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Baby Ruth Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/baby-ruth-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532562077" alt="Baby Ruth American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>Freshly roasted peanuts, caramel and chocolate flavored nougat, smothered in a generous coating of milk chocolate, is what makes this bar truly wonderful! First introduced in 1920, the Babe Ruth Bar is a delightful taste of an old fashioned candy treat. This American Chocolate Bar was long thought to be named after the famous baseball player Babe Ruth. Not true. The Babe Ruth chocolate bar got it's name from President Grover Cleveland's daughter, Ruth. This is a substantial chocolate bar that satisfies any craving for chocolate.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/butterfinger-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Butterfinger" rel="noopener noreferrer">Butterfinger</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/butterfinger-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532562301" alt="Butterfinger American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>What could be better than a Butterfinger Chocolate Bar? This bar is triumphant in it's crispy and crunchy, peanut buttery texture. With it's crunchy peanut butter center it is only heightened by the milk chocolate it's surrounded in. The sweet and slightly salty peanut middle really makes the pure taste of the milk chocolate pop out. It's a perfect play on both textures, and is incredible paired together. The Butterfinger Chocolate Bar came out in 1923 and has been a favorite chocolate bar for many. The love for this bar spans the generations. Young and old all love that crisp bite of a Butterfinger!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/milk-way-candy-bars" target="_blank" title="Milky Way Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Milky Way Bar</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/milky-way-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532562442" alt="Milky Way American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>Milky Way chocolate bars are a classic indulgence. Starting out in 1923, this American Chocolate Bar was originally meant to resemble the taste of malted milk which at the time was a very popular choice of drink. We don't go for the drink anymore, but we'll take this delicious chocolate bar any day! Milky Way is a chocolate covered bar with a caramel and nougat center. The nougat is just right, with it's creamy and airy consistency along with the ribbon of caramel which is generous enough to taste and does not get lost in the nougat or milk chocolate. Milky Way are classic American Chocolate Bars that will keep customers coming back for more!</div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#8. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/american-chocolate-bars" target="_blank" title="Reese's Peanut Butter Cups" rel="noopener noreferrer">Reese's Peanut Butter Cups</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/reeses-peanut-butter-cups-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532562758" alt="Reese's Peanut Butter Cups American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>When it comes to <span>Reese's Peanut Butter Cups, we love the American version and so will your customers! And o</span>ne cup just will not do! Most fans could probably eat 10 cups and not tire of their exquisite taste. Reese's Peanut Butter Cups are an old fashioned candy treat that came out in 1928. They may be old but they've stuck around for good reason, because they are delicious! A delicious milk chocolate cup that is filled with a creamy and smooth peanut butter. It sounds so simple but the pair of these two flavors are nothing short of magical in your mouth! This dynamic duo sync up beautifully with the faint saltiness of the peanut butter combined with the rich milk chocolate. It makes this snack incredibly enticing. American <span>Reese's Peanut Butter Cups</span> are a must have addition to every single chocolate section!</div>
<div></div>
<h3></h3>
<h3>#9.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/whatchamacallit-candy-bar" target="_blank" title="Whatchamacallit Bar" rel="noopener noreferrer">Whatchamacallit Bar</a>
</h3>
<p> <img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/whatchamacallit-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532563165" alt="Whatchamacallit American Chocolate Bars Wholesale Candy Canada"></p>
<div>The <span>Whatchamacallit Bar</span> is so delicious they probably lost their minds trying to name it. Anything this delicious can make you speechless! The Whatchamacallit is a mix of buttery, crunchy sweet and salty. It covers every need and craving of your taste buds! Inside the <span>Whatchamacallit Bar</span> is a peanut flavored crisp along with the chewiest caramel that is covered in milk chocolate. This bar packs a flavorful punch of yumminess with it's multiple flavors and textures. A very satisfying Chocolate Bar that will entice your customers. A unique bar that is sure to peak hungry interest.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10.Hershey's Milk Chocolate Bar </h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/hersheys-milk-chocolate-bar-american-chocolate-bars-wholesale-candy.png?v=1532563337" alt="Hershey's Milk Chocolate Bar-Candy Wholesale Canada"></p>
<div>If there was one must have American Chocolate Bar, this would be the one! The Hershey Milk Chocolate Bar came out in 1900. Old fashioned but delicious, this bar never goes out of style! Classic and not complicated. Just pure and simple. This bar is referred to as " The Great American Chocolate Bar", probably because of it's simplicity. Hershey's Chocolate is said to be specially tangy. That may be why there are so many big fanatics of this chocolate. This American Chocolate bar is a staple for many chocolate lovers. A great bar to have in your chocolate section!</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"></h3>
<div>American Chocolate Bars can be a hard to find item for many of your customers. Make your store their number one stop for their American Chocolate Bars craving!<span> Check out our fresh selection of American Chocolate Bars all available at wholesale prices!</span>
</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/american-chocolate-bars" target="_blank" title="American Chocolate Bars at Wholesale Prices" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>American Chocolate Bars at Wholesale Prices</span></a></h3>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-these-top-10-retro-candies</id>
    <published>2018-07-16T19:39:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-07-16T22:12:57-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-these-top-10-retro-candies"/>
    <title>Your Store Needs These Top 10 Retro Candies</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<span>Relive all the best days with our Retro Candy! We have your favorite old fashioned candy all at wholesale prices. When any Candy Lover walks down the aisle of your store they'll be delighted and eager to taste all the retro candy from their youth.</span><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/your-store-needs-these-top-10-retro-candies">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 style="text-align: center;">Every Candy Section needs Retro Candies</h2>
<div>Relive all the best days with our Retro Candy! We have your favorite old fashioned candy all at wholesale prices. When any Candy Lover walks down the aisle of your store they'll be delighted and eager to taste all the retro candy from their youth.</div>
<div>We love Retro Candy. We eat lots of it! We've made a list of the top 10 must have Retro Candies. Get ready to feel nostalgic and hungry!</div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<h3>#1. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/pop-rocks" target="_blank" title="Pop Rocks Popping Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Pop Rocks Popping Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/pop-rocks-popping-candy-retro-candies.png?v=1531777909" alt="Pop Rocks Popping Candy-Retro Candies"></p>
<div>For that fun and explosive feeling there is no other Retro Candy that compares to Pop Rocks. These tiny little bits of  exploding candy really do pop in your mouth. You not only get the delicious taste, but that exciting and fun feeling that goes along with Pop Rocks. This old fashioned candy came out in 1975 and they've been popular ever since. This popping and unique candy lets you taste the explosion in nine flavors, Blue Razz Pop Rocks, Green Apple Pop Rocks, Grape Pop Rocks, Strawberry Pop Rocks,Tropical Punch Pop Rocks, Watermelon Pop Rocks, Cotton Candy Explosion Pop Rocks, Bubble Gum Pop Rocks, and of course the Original Pop Rocks.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#2.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-bottle-caps-rolls" target="_blank" title="Bottle Caps Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Bottle Caps Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/wonka-bottle-caps-soda-pop-candy-retro-candies.png?v=1531778544" alt="Wonka Bottle Caps Soda Pop Candy"></p>
<div>These sweet and tart tablet like candies are on everyone's must eat list! Bottle Caps are a Retro Candy that was first introduced to us in 1972. They are based on the 1971 film, Willy Wonka And The Chocolate Factory. They've been delighting us for generations! Bottle Caps Candy are made to actually look like metal soda bottle caps. They not only resemble cool looking retro bottle caps but really taste like all of our favorite soft drinks. The flavors in a roll of Bottle Caps are Root Beer, Cherry, Grape, Cola and Orange. </div>
<div> </div>
<h3>#3.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/charleston-chew-candy-bars-chocolate" target="_blank" title="Charleston Chew" rel="noopener noreferrer">Charleston Chew</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/charleston-chew-retro-candy.png?v=1531778880" alt="Charleston Chew Retro Candy"></p>
<div>This old fashioned candy came out in 1922. Charleston Chew made the "roaring 20's" even sweeter! Charleston Chew Candy is made of irresistible smooth nougat that is then coated in a luscious and rich layer of chocolate. Some people like to freeze them and then crack them as they eat them. Charleston Chew is enjoyable either way. This Retro Candy is sure capture the attention of any candy lover. These nougat bars come in classic flavors, Chocolate, Strawberry and Vanilla. Rediscover the good old days with Charleston Chew!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#4.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/gold-mine-bubble-gum" target="_blank" title="Gold Mine Bubble Gum" rel="noopener noreferrer">Gold Mine Bubble Gum</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/gold-mine-bubble-gum-retro-candy.png?v=1531779764" alt="Gold Mine Bubble Gum Retro Candy"></p>
<div>These little yellow coloured nuggets really do like like gold, and they even come in a cute little re-usable burlap pouch. You're candy section will hit the jackpot with this old time Bubble Gum! Gold Mine Bubble Gum is as juicy and flavorful as you remember. Introduce it to the younger generations. Guaranteed they've never seen anything quite like it. This Bubblegum is worth it's wait in gold!</div>
<div></div>
<div></div>
<h3>#5.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/charms-blow-pop" target="_blank" title="Charms Blow Pop" rel="noopener noreferrer">Charms Blow Pop</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/charms-blow-pop-bubblegum-lollipops-retro-candy.png?v=1531780922" alt="Charms Blow Pop Bubble Gum Lollipops Retro Candy"></p>
<div>A Lollipop with a Bubble Gum  surprise in the middle, this Retro Lollipop really is double whammy treat! Charms Blow Pops will fill your store with smiles all around. The Charms Blow Pop came out in 1969 and was a top selling candy right from the start. These old fashioned mouthwatering Lollipops will satisfy any candy connoisseur, a great selling Candy that all your customers will love. </div>
<div></div>
<h3>#6.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/nerds-candy" target="_blank" title="Nerds Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Nerds Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/nerds-candy-retro-candies-1970s.png?v=1531781476" alt="Nerds Candy"></p>
<div>Small but mighty! Nerds Candy are tangy, delicious and so crunchy. These little bits of candy are a groovy taste from the 1970's. Nerds Candy have been enjoyed for years. You probably ate them as a child and now your very own children eat them. There's something "Scrumdiddlyumtious" as Willy Wonka would say about this cool Retro Candy. Nerds Candy come with two flavors in one box, another bonus with this candy. Eat them one side at a time or have fun mixing them up. Nerds come in the coolest of flavors. There are Nerds Watermelon And Cherry, Nerds Surf And Turf, Nerds Double Dipped Flavors, Nerds Wild Berry And Peach, Nerds Grape And Strawberry. The newest addition to the Nerds Candy are Nerd Ropes. These are a long and slender chewy piece of gummy candy that is completely covered in nerds. A great tasting combination. Nerd Ropes come in Very Berry and Rainbow.</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#7.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/big-league-chew" target="_blank" title="Big League Chew" rel="noopener noreferrer">Big League Chew</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/big-league-chew-bubble-gum.png?v=1531782284" alt="Big League Chew Bubble Gum"></p>
<div>This Retro Bubble Gum is always a home run! Big League Chew was invented by baseball players in 1980 and has been an iconic bubblegum ever since. This bubblegum comes in a shredded form inside of a pouch and was originally meant to replace that yucky chewing tobacco. A delicious alternative that also blows the best and biggest bubbles! Big League Chew makes us all feel like we're in the "Big Leagues"!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#8.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/products/wonka-fundip" target="_blank" title="Fun Dip Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Fun Dip Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/fun-dip-retro-candy-willy-wonka.png?v=1531782567" alt="Fun Dip Retro Candy from Willy Wonka and the Chocolate Factory"></p>
<div>Another Wonka Favorite! This Retro Candy is nothing short of delicious playfulness! Comes in a pouch and a sweet candy stick to use for dipping and licking into the sensational tasting powdered candy. Fun Dip comes in two flavors, Razz Apple Magic Dip and Cherry Yum Diddly Dip. Fun Dip is an expected candy for any Candy Lover, a staple Retro candy that your never too old to eat!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#9.<a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/life-savers-candy" target="_blank" title="Life Savers Candy" rel="noopener noreferrer">Life Savers Candy</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/life-savers-retro-candy.png?v=1531783135" alt="Life Savers Retro Candy"></p>
<div>This roll of Retro Candy is really a Life Saver. This nostalgic candy can freshen your breath, or give you that afternoon pick me up. Life Savers came out in 1912, a real old fashioned candy that every customer has come to anticipate. This Retro Candy comes in a variety of mouthwatering flavors and have become a classic candy that have been loved through many generations. A roll of Life Savers in your pocket is sure way to have a sweet day!</div>
<div></div>
<h3>#10. <a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/haribo-candy" target="_blank" title="Haribo Gold Bears" rel="noopener noreferrer">Haribo Gold Bears</a>
</h3>
<p><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/haribo-gold-bears-retro-candy.png?v=1531783444" alt="Haribo Gold Bears Gummy Candy"></p>
<div>"Welcome to the Happy World Of Haribo". Everybody is smiling when they eat this Gummy Candy. Haribo Gold Bears came out in the early 1920's and ever since their arrival the world has truly been "happily" indulging in them. Every bite of this Retro Candy is bursting with the best and fruitiest of flavors. Haribo Gold Bears<span> come in Original and Sour. Every Gummy Candy lover will come back time and time again for these gummy bears!</span>
</div>
<h3 style="text-align: center;"><a href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/collections/retro-candy" target="_blank" title="Check out all the Retro Candy Here" rel="noopener noreferrer"><span>Check out all the Retro Candy Here</span></a></h3>
<div>
<div></div>
<div>These are just a few of our top selling Retro Candies. Be sure to check out our whole collection of Retro Candies. You'll be glad you did, and so will your customers that crave a taste of that good old fashioned nostalgia in their candy!</div>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-importance-of-candy-in-your-store</id>
    <published>2016-08-22T20:00:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2018-07-16T15:52:09-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-importance-of-candy-in-your-store"/>
    <title>The Importance of Candy in Your Store</title>
    <author>
      <name>Candy Queen</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;"></div>
<div style="text-align: center;">
<span>At </span><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">iwholesalecandy.ca</a><span> we will keep your candy section fully stocked </span><span>with our fresh, delicious wholesale candy! </span><span>Keep those candy lovers coming back for more, and let us help your </span><span>store become the sweetest destination!</span>
</div><p><a class="read-more" href="https://iwholesalecandy.ca/blogs/sweet-candy-news/the-importance-of-candy-in-your-store">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h1 style="text-align: center;"><span>Fresh Candy at Wholesale Prices</span></h1>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Wholesale Candy Canada-Lollipop Display" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/iwholesalecandy-candy-store-display.jpg?6704034036515448919" style="float: none;"></p>
<h2 style="text-align: center;">Add Excitement to Your Candy Section!</h2>
<p><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">i</a><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">wholesalecandy.ca</a><span>  will help make your store a favorite place to shop </span><span>for candy! You will not only surprise all your regular customers by </span><span>offering them something new and exciting, but you will attract a new </span><span>customer base in the process!</span><br><span>They'll be coming from everywhere to visit your store as they notice </span><span>the fresh selection of your new and delicious candy, and most </span><span>importantly they'll be coming back again and again!</span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img alt="Wholesale Candy Canada-iwholesalecandy.ca" src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/iwholesalecandy-candy-store_large.jpg?5319298809726409425" style="float: none;"></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Candy is the Most Important Category</h3>
<p><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">iwholesalecandy.ca</a><span> will help your business stand out, </span><span>don't be like all the other stores who only stock the same old, run of </span><span>the mill candy. The customers will be bored, and so will your sales. </span><span>If you want to attract more customers and increase your stores </span><span>traffic, entice them with our fresh selection of wholesale candy. At </span><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">iwholesalecandy.ca</a><span> we will gladly assist you in achieving these goals. </span><span>The more selection of candy your store carries, creates greater </span><span>opportunity for you to </span><span>grow your business. You only have one chance to make a good first </span><span>impression, make it a sweet one!</span><br><span>We take great pride in our outstanding customer service, and will make </span><span>sure you are completely satisfied with our service. We know the vital </span><span>importance of being able to offer the very best quality of candy.</span></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">
<br>Do you have the candy your customers love?</h3>
<p style="text-align: center;"><img src="//cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/1435/0472/files/iwholesalecandy-everyone-loves-candy.jpg?9315102480231396559" alt="iWholesaleCandy.ca Everyone Loves Candy"></p>
<h3 style="text-align: center;">Outstanding Customer Service</h3>
<p><span>At </span><a href="http://iwholesalecandy.ca/" data-saferedirecturl="https://www.google.com/url?hl=en&amp;q=http://iwholesalecandy.ca&amp;source=gmail&amp;ust=1471996558336000&amp;usg=AFQjCNGhzxKH1ha1DcoQ2BVND6Vhh67kuA" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">iwholesalecandy.ca</a><span> we will keep your candy section fully stocked </span><span>with our fresh, delicious wholesale candy! </span><span>Keep those candy lovers coming back for more, and let us help your </span><span>store become the sweetest destination!</span></p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
